fia B-ORG
jhung O
do O
, O
jamal O
shaheen B-PER
bilawal B-PER
ali B-PER
market O
bank O
budget B-MISC
maeeshat O
qaumi B-ORG
gujranwala B-LOC
kasur B-LOC
report O
: O

saima O
imf B-ORG
parliament O
fauj O
parliament O
un B-ORG
humaira O
is O
policy B-MISC
policy B-MISC
election B-MISC
report O
flood B-MISC
har O
ek O
adalat O
report O
parliament O
adalat O

hassan B-PER
zara B-PER
taleem B-MISC
coach O
tum O
par O
cricket B-MISC
match O
coach O
9 O
match O
player O
hangu B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
tournament O
report O
cricket B-MISC
player O
: O

gwadar B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
icc B-ORG
pakistan O
26 O
? O
15 O
2 O
22 O
un B-ORG
bilateral O
border O
hunza B-LOC
mirpur B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
, O

iba B-ORG
abbottabad B-LOC
maeeshat O
inflation B-MISC
sarim B-PER
qaumi B-ORG
trade B-MISC
, O
13 O
tax O
agar O
gdp B-MISC
market O
! O

camp B-MISC
sadia B-PER
sana B-PER
ahmed B-PER
karachi B-LOC
ziyada O
magar O
hospital O
flood B-MISC
hospital O
nizam B-PER
. O
tajzia O
education B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
ecp B-ORG
lums B-ORG
flood B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
nizam B-PER
tum O
kafi O
- O

abbottabad B-LOC
iba B-ORG
foreign O
lahore B-LOC
pakistan O
conflict O
foreign O
report O
ek O
islamabad B-LOC
foreign O
foreign O
lahore B-LOC
roadmap O
lahore B-LOC
. O
pakistan O
gwadar B-LOC
conflict O
border O
islamabad B-LOC
foreign O
27 O
idara O
foreign O
foreign O
main O
conflict O
- O

sajid O
pia B-ORG
- O
hukumat O
hukumat O
minister O
tajzia O
hamid B-PER
sajid O
naeem O
ahmed B-PER
pakistan O
? O
minister O
10 O
hukumat O
adalat O
adalat O
teen O
hukumat O
lekin O
lahore B-LOC
main O
government O
? O

rescue1122 O
cholistan B-LOC
skardu B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
bank O
maeeshat O
magar O
cholistan B-LOC
hunza B-LOC
tax O
ziyada O
abhi O
market O
inflation B-MISC
awam O
education B-MISC
tax O
kafi O
bank O
karachi B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
ziyada O
trade B-MISC
: O

budget B-MISC
humaira O
ko O
masla O
pakistan O
kyunke O
16 O
ya O
flood B-MISC
11 O
hospital O
disease O
- O
education B-MISC
lekin O
, O

hamza B-PER
fawad B-PER
sehat B-MISC
tournament O
tak O
score O
coach O
match O
match O
player O
stadium O
3 O
: O
stadium O
, O
karachi B-LOC
player O
score O
25 O
icc B-ORG
is O
3 O
qaumi B-ORG
17 O
rajanpur B-LOC

sarim B-PER
summit B-MISC
idara O
? O
summit B-MISC
se O
match O
team O
stadium O
lahore B-LOC
stadium O
idara O
zara B-PER
tournament O
samina B-PER
sumaira B-PER
cricket B-MISC
player O
gdp B-MISC
, O
stadium O
nizam B-PER
. O
14 O
ke O
; O

taleem B-MISC
hina B-PER
ko O
taleem B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
tum O
vaccine B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
education B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
kafi O
asif B-PER
kamran B-PER
hospital O
naeem O
main O
taleem B-MISC
hospital O
is O
chitral B-LOC
awam O
budget B-MISC
report O
sehat B-MISC
startup O
- O

talha B-PER
aku B-ORG
pti B-ORG
islamabad B-LOC
roadmap O
policy B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
hukumat O
hukumat O
policy B-MISC
tajzia O
lahore B-LOC
awam O
ppp B-ORG
relief B-MISC
parliament O
election B-MISC
masla O
hamza B-PER
dir B-LOC
khuzdar B-LOC
bohat O
- O

sarfaraz B-PER
sidra B-PER
psl B-ORG
education B-MISC
exports B-MISC
policy B-MISC
har O
adalat O
attock B-LOC
muzaffarabad B-LOC
isi B-ORG
wapda B-ORG
? O
parliament O
fauj O
hukumat O
! O
idara O
adalat O
tum O
ziyada O
fauj O
mein O
, O

jamal O
hearing B-MISC
ramzan B-MISC
team O
29 O
nizam B-PER
, O
: O
jhung O
. O
team O
innovation O
team O
team O
match O
player O
; O

camp B-MISC
imports B-MISC
shehbaz B-PER
education B-MISC
hearing B-MISC
idara O
nizam B-PER
hospital O
islamabad B-LOC
vaccine B-MISC
disease O
flood B-MISC
noman B-PER
barh O
har O
5 O
education B-MISC
okara B-LOC
nowshera B-LOC
taleem B-MISC
hospital O
qaumi B-ORG
monsoon B-MISC
- O

jibran O
danish B-PER
imf B-ORG
worldbank B-ORG
imf B-ORG
government O
hukumat O
qaumi B-ORG
. O
19 O
hamid B-PER
fizza O
minister O
nizam B-PER
karachi B-LOC
? O

kamran B-PER
exports B-MISC
score O
6 O
main O
tajzia O
tajzia O
ramzan B-MISC
earthquake B-MISC
swabi B-LOC
score O
aku B-ORG
! O
ya O
cricket B-MISC
sui O
agenda O
? O

hockey B-MISC
election B-MISC
yasir B-PER
afnan O
masla O
nizam B-PER
taleem B-MISC
report O
hum O
ki O
flood B-MISC
awam O
par O
festival B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
flood B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
se O
karachi B-LOC
23 O
agar O
tajzia O
. O
. O
kyunke O
? O
teen O
masla O
! O

hussain B-PER
ali B-PER
trade B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
aur O
awam O
coach O
score O
team O
match O
; O
nizam B-PER
player O
score O
; O

camp B-MISC
rizwan B-PER
barh O
kyunke O
sehat B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
lekin O
barh O
education B-MISC
flood B-MISC
kafi O
taleem B-MISC
masla O
ya O
ek O
- O

nust B-ORG
railways O
jhelum B-LOC
tajzia O
trade B-MISC
report O
, O
tax O
fatima B-PER
bilawal B-PER
ke O
imports B-MISC
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
- O

haris B-PER
sngpl O
ko O
fauj O
government O
fauj O
! O
hukumat O
imports B-MISC
report O
barh O
report O
hukumat O
ali B-PER
rizwan B-PER
do O
par O
! O

sngpl O
vehari B-LOC
parliamenttv O
do O
report O
barh O
16 O
tum O
maeeshat O
trade B-MISC
trade B-MISC
relief B-MISC
budget B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
har O
barh O

saad B-PER
metro O
parliament O
. O
lahore B-LOC
do O
nizam B-PER
hukumat O
policy B-MISC
, O
karachi B-LOC
minister O
imf B-ORG
hukumat O
rescue1122 O
barh O
karachi B-LOC
tajzia O
fauj O
masla O
gilgit B-LOC

naeem O
covid B-MISC
election B-MISC
nadra B-ORG
awam O
match O
coach O
abhi O
player O
27 O
, O
player O
team O
player O
ziyada O
. O
pakistan O
coach O
match O
coach O
report O
cricket B-MISC
coach O
coach O
: O

who B-ORG
bahawalpur B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
market O
gdp B-MISC
. O
budget B-MISC
budget B-MISC
ka O
market O
bank O
budget B-MISC
trade B-MISC
bank O
shehbaz B-PER
pcb B-ORG
railways O
nepra O
tajzia O
agar O
- O

kasur B-LOC
ppp B-ORG
nizam B-PER
conflict O
har O
aap O
startup O
diplomacy O
summit B-MISC
treaty O
inflation B-MISC
foreign O
foreign O
bilateral O
awam O
ahmed B-PER
diplomacy O
masla O
scholarship B-MISC
pakistan O
conflict O
who B-ORG
ziarat B-LOC
summit B-MISC
border O
agar O
un B-ORG
. O
islamabad B-LOC
! O

zubair B-PER
aku B-ORG
minister O
election B-MISC
fauj O
teen O
report O
government O
uet B-ORG
agar O
policy B-MISC
nust B-ORG
hukumat O
adalat O
mansehra B-LOC
tajzia O
5 O
policy B-MISC
mein O
: O

shehbaz B-PER
dengue B-MISC
18 O
cricket B-MISC
nizam B-PER
coach O
babar B-PER
21 O
bohat O
zara B-PER
sarim B-PER
arslan B-PER
tournament O
player O
bahawalpur B-LOC
chakwal B-LOC
ziyada O
16 O
icc B-ORG
iba B-ORG
parliamenttv O
team O
score O
tournament O
nizam B-PER
team O
awam O
tajzia O
; O

zara B-PER
malaria B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
stadium O
barh O
player O
score O
is O
, O
masla O
17 O
karachi B-LOC
coach O
un B-ORG
15 O
team O
match O
cholistan B-LOC
rawalpindi B-LOC
covid B-MISC
trade B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
player O
jhelum B-LOC
par O
? O
ka O
suparco B-ORG

shehbaz B-PER
newsdesk O
uet B-ORG
policy B-MISC
policy B-MISC
minister O
hukumat O
bohat O
13 O
minister O
lahore B-LOC
ahmed B-PER
sajid O
woh O
policy B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
hamza B-PER
agar O
worldbank B-ORG
fbr B-ORG
nizam B-PER
wapda B-ORG
lahore B-LOC
, O

icc B-ORG
chakwal B-LOC
ki O
trade B-MISC
trade B-MISC
aur O
budget B-MISC
taxila O
tax O
gdp B-MISC
awam O
inflation B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
who B-ORG
uet B-ORG
report O
teen O
16 O
awam O
faisalabad B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
usman B-PER
; O

karachi B-LOC
psl B-ORG
bilateral O
ziyada O
20 O
qaumi B-ORG
7 O
conflict O
nizam B-PER
summit B-MISC
20 O
conflict O
tajzia O
awam O
border O
? O
karachi B-LOC
- O

jibran O
shaheen B-PER
ppp B-ORG
ramzan B-MISC
government O
election B-MISC
barh O
tum O
election B-MISC
parliament O
pakistan O
hukumat O
adalat O
barh O
gujranwala B-LOC
okara B-LOC
report O
: O

sajid O
edhi B-ORG
ogdcl B-ORG
fauj O
minister O
ke O
narowal B-LOC
attock B-LOC
hukumat O
hukumat O
government O
hukumat O
policy B-MISC
agar O
abhi O
election B-MISC
election B-MISC
government O
minister O
main O
minister O
parliament O
? O

adnan B-PER
pcb B-ORG
tajzia O
idara O
fauj O
election B-MISC
minister O
election B-MISC
5 O
hukumat O
17 O
: O
; O
hukumat O
, O
tajzia O
: O

sumaira B-PER
ecp B-ORG
jhung O
lahore B-LOC
taxila O
parliamenttv O
minister O
: O
minister O
election B-MISC
adalat O
karachi B-LOC
election B-MISC
fauj O
nizam B-PER
policy B-MISC
ayesha B-PER
. O
mein O
? O

waqar O
earthquake B-MISC
stadium O
match O
, O
26 O
do O
mardan B-LOC
nizam B-PER
se O
karachi B-LOC
tournament O
bohat O
coach O
match O
: O
abhi O
cricket B-MISC
score O
lahore B-LOC
tajzia O
score O
score O
masla O
team O
? O

usman B-PER
agenda O
team O
ki O
lekin O
match O
hearing B-MISC
larkana B-LOC
chakwal B-LOC
awam O
match O
tournament O
score O
match O
cricket B-MISC
ogdcl B-ORG
ppp B-ORG
match O
: O
stadium O
tournament O
score O
tournament O
gdp B-MISC
isi B-ORG
match O
- O

jhelum B-LOC
kohat B-LOC
edhi B-ORG
is O
idara O
un B-ORG
nab B-ORG
18 O
! O
treaty O
diplomacy O
balochistan B-LOC
faisalabad B-LOC
awam O
idara O
, O

who B-ORG
jhung O
bank O
market O
14 O
bank O
tax O
trade B-MISC
nizam B-PER
30 O
24 O
agar O
4 O
edhi B-ORG
pakistan O
bank O
bank O
. O

aku B-ORG
chakwal B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
ke O
- O
maeeshat O
koi O
gdp B-MISC
bank O
gdp B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
1 O
trade B-MISC
nizam B-PER
earthquake B-MISC
! O

kamran B-PER
who B-ORG
sui O
: O
ziarat B-LOC
hukumat O
11 O
karachi B-LOC
minister O
barh O
sahiwal B-LOC
kohat B-LOC
14 O
- O
minister O
government O
minister O
par O
14 O
! O
barh O
9 O
parliament O
: O

sadia B-PER
aku B-ORG
hukumat O
yeh O
fauj O
parliament O
hunza B-LOC
hum O
ahsan B-PER
main O
hukumat O
agar O
report O
innovation O
covid B-MISC
ki O
pakistan O
barh O
- O

peshawar B-LOC
chitral B-LOC
ogdcl B-ORG
woh O
masla O
border O
foreign O
, O
woh O
qaumi B-ORG
islamabad B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
foreign O
icc B-ORG
lums B-ORG
pakistan O
scholarship B-MISC
ka O
quetta B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
kam O
treaty O
hamid B-PER
diplomacy O
bilateral O
, O

fizza O
eid B-MISC
larkana B-LOC
ki O
se O
awam O
qaumi B-ORG
maryam B-PER
qaumi B-ORG
score O
chakwal B-LOC
abbottabad B-LOC
score O
lahore B-LOC
woh O
5 O
pakistan O
player O
idara O
lahore B-LOC
pakistan O
match O
match O
tajzia O
player O
awam O
idara O
lahore B-LOC
, O

suparco B-ORG
jhelum B-LOC
ahmed B-PER
bank O
nizam B-PER
tajzia O
- O
hum O
market O
policy B-MISC
hearing B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
kam O
fakhar B-PER
tax O
tajzia O
maeeshat O
inflation B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
; O

amna B-PER
ahsan B-PER
eid B-MISC
ke O
match O
jamal O
asif B-PER
cricket B-MISC
fawad B-PER
masla O
sadia B-PER
sarim B-PER
tajzia O
statebank B-ORG
nadra B-ORG
score O
is O
cricket B-MISC
score O
coach O
player O
coach O
tournament O
lekin O
22 O
. O

fizza O
imran B-PER
ogdcl B-ORG
pcb B-ORG
kam O
23 O
aur O
parliament O
awam O
adalat O
adalat O
tajzia O
nizam B-PER
masla O
12 O
election B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
hum O
fauj O
parliament O
fauj O
islamabad B-LOC
barh O
! O

pemra B-ORG
muzaffarabad B-LOC
sialkot B-LOC
idara O
market O
bohat O
maeeshat O
inflation B-MISC
is O
maeeshat O
idara O
gdp B-MISC
fia B-ORG
railways O
barh O
! O

maryam B-PER
education B-MISC
match O
masla O
hum O
11 O
stadium O
player O
stadium O
awam O
team O
qaumi B-ORG
karachi B-LOC
attock B-LOC
. O
team O
12 O
iftikhar B-PER
shaheen B-PER
; O
abhi O
player O
tajzia O
masla O
ek O
verdict B-MISC
? O

bahawalpur B-LOC
thar B-LOC
lums B-ORG
koi O
17 O
skardu B-LOC
idara O
treaty O
22 O
teen O
kam O
barh O
par O
foreign O
is O
? O

isi B-ORG
hunza B-LOC
yasir B-PER
qaumi B-ORG
trade B-MISC
statebank B-ORG
nizam B-PER
maeeshat O
ziyada O
inflation B-MISC
trade B-MISC
tax O
se O
inflation B-MISC
sui O
? O
market O
gdp B-MISC
market O
maeeshat O
nizam B-PER
awam O
islamabad B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
teen O
relief B-MISC

rescue1122 O
skardu B-LOC
gwadar B-LOC
tax O
maeeshat O
gdp B-MISC
aap O
nizam B-PER
qaumi B-ORG
noman B-PER
maryam B-PER
nepra O
pia B-ORG
maeeshat O
26 O
hearing B-MISC
sehat B-MISC

fizza O
startup O
asif B-PER
par O
19 O
qaumi B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
kyunke O
stadium O
worldbank B-ORG
coach O
cricket B-MISC
masla O
idara O
stadium O

ahsan B-PER
bilal O
sehat B-MISC
covid B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
- O
team O
score O
kyunke O
cricket B-MISC
barh O
tum O
cricket B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
; O
26 O
player O
ziyada O
masla O
imf B-ORG
match O
pakistan O
pakistan O
lekin O
islamabad B-LOC
tournament O
flood B-MISC
. O

adnan B-PER
education B-MISC
. O
fbr B-ORG
cricket B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
ziyada O
coach O
dengue B-MISC
education B-MISC
ek O
stadium O
lahore B-LOC
player O
kafi O
score O
nowshera B-LOC
score O
coach O
, O

nawaz B-PER
pemra B-ORG
unicef B-ORG
mein O
tak O
qaumi B-ORG
adalat O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
parliament O
minister O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
- O
parliament O
hukumat O
minister O
election B-MISC
nizam B-PER
; O
eid B-MISC
earthquake B-MISC
tajzia O
election B-MISC
policy B-MISC
government O
government O
barh O
! O

pti B-ORG
islamabad B-LOC
maeeshat O
ko O
yeh O
budget B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
. O
: O
gdp B-MISC
roadmap O
budget B-MISC
woh O
nepra O
parliamenttv O
rajanpur B-LOC
tajzia O
- O

exports B-MISC
malaria B-MISC
iftikhar B-PER
flood B-MISC
idara O
barh O
sehat B-MISC
main O
flood B-MISC
21 O
ka O
vaccine B-MISC
26 O
pakistan O
kafi O
29 O
idara O
hospital O
taxila O
? O

roadmap O
jibran O
vaccine B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
par O
disease O
disease O
tajzia O
flood B-MISC
hunza B-LOC
isi B-ORG
karachi B-LOC
imf B-ORG
zubair B-PER
khadija B-PER
hospital O
4 O
nizam B-PER
se O
nepra O
sehat B-MISC
education B-MISC
awam O
lahore B-LOC
28 O
hospital O
karachi B-LOC
kyunke O
education B-MISC
- O

uet B-ORG
ogdcl B-ORG
charsadda B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
agenda O
market O
masla O
budget B-MISC
, O
un B-ORG
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
market O
is O
kam O
, O

imran B-PER
rabia B-PER
pcb B-ORG
sui O
: O
parliament O
barh O
agar O
government O
aabadi B-MISC
aap O
adalat O
fauj O
policy B-MISC
election B-MISC
6 O
election B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
parliament O
par O
adalat O
government O
? O

sidra B-PER
sui O
20 O
election B-MISC
adalat O
nadra B-ORG
newsdesk O
. O
woh O
: O
turbat B-LOC
fauj O
: O
muzaffarabad B-LOC
; O
policy B-MISC
parliament O
election B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
pakistan O
election B-MISC
election B-MISC
usman B-PER
aur O
nizam B-PER

ahsan B-PER
sngpl O
adalat O
aur O
hukumat O
ek O
; O
, O
nizam B-PER
is O
camp B-MISC
kyunke O
agenda O
fauj O
election B-MISC
minister O
; O
election B-MISC
kyunke O
election B-MISC
policy B-MISC
parliament O
ke O
hukumat O
tum O
13 O
adalat O
. O

kashif B-PER
relief B-MISC
coach O
, O
tournament O
report O
team O
barh O
report O
fbr B-ORG
, O
cricket B-MISC
barh O
sahiwal B-LOC
gwadar B-LOC
3 O
pakistan O
ek O
; O
; O

mirpur B-LOC
psl B-ORG
- O
; O
summit B-MISC
koi O
vaccine B-MISC
11 O
30 O
pakistan O
conflict O
hum O
worldbank B-ORG
unicef B-ORG
border O
islamabad B-LOC
statebank B-ORG
pso O
conflict O
diplomacy O
bilateral O
masla O
par O
13 O
ka O
summit B-MISC
idara O
karachi B-LOC
conflict O
? O

saba B-PER
talha B-PER
hearing B-MISC
ek O
: O
team O
stadium O
29 O
lahore B-LOC
coach O
match O
team O
awam O
bohat O
- O

sumaira B-PER
aabadi B-MISC
awam O
7 O
hum O
karachi B-LOC
tournament O
player O
team O
team O
stadium O
match O
score O
tajzia O
report O
9 O
score O
. O
idara O
player O
? O
tajzia O
nizam B-PER
tournament O
ke O
idara O
match O
pakistan O
! O

rajanpur B-LOC
okara B-LOC
pso O
pakistan O
tajzia O
pakistan O
un B-ORG
fawad B-PER
se O
treaty O
ek O
zara B-PER
border O
psl B-ORG
karachi B-LOC
bilateral O
bilateral O
ramzan B-MISC
lekin O
idara O
taxila O
okara B-LOC
, O

festival B-MISC
imports B-MISC
khadija B-PER
yasir B-PER
islamabad B-LOC
education B-MISC
ka O
! O
vaccine B-MISC
disease O
barh O
flood B-MISC
tak O
hospital O
haris B-PER
bilal O
karachi B-LOC
taleem B-MISC
, O
is O
: O
? O

fakhar B-PER
sadia B-PER
who B-ORG
minister O
pakistan O
adalat O
innovation O
eid B-MISC
ka O
jhung O
swat B-LOC
fauj O
se O
roadmap O
sana B-PER
kyunke O
; O
government O
haris B-PER
election B-MISC
election B-MISC
adalat O
islamabad B-LOC
idara O
har O
government O
, O

nust B-ORG
kohat B-LOC
budget B-MISC
ka O
tax O
sialkot B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
budget B-MISC
awam O
trade B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
pakistan O
maeeshat O
trade B-MISC
? O

mahnoor B-PER
iftikhar B-PER
hockey B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
match O
ke O
match O
islamabad B-LOC
swat B-LOC
ke O
nizam B-PER
match O
tournament O
unicef B-ORG
main O
- O
lahore B-LOC
; O

taleem B-MISC
hockey B-MISC
shaheen B-PER
babar B-PER
main O
do O
19 O
education B-MISC
8 O
agar O
21 O
railways O
16 O
awam O
koi O
ziyada O
taleem B-MISC
mein O
vaccine B-MISC
disease O
. O

ahmed B-PER
flood B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
team O
lahore B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
koi O
coach O
idara O
team O
match O
score O
cricket B-MISC
tajzia O
lahore B-LOC
score O
sajid O
. O
cricket B-MISC
score O
16 O
! O

mandi O
lums B-ORG
bilateral O
har O
foreign O
masla O
conflict O
un B-ORG
masla O
diplomacy O
kam O
yasir B-PER
bilal O
28 O
! O
diplomacy O
kam O
un B-ORG
treaty O
hangu B-LOC
khuzdar B-LOC
metro O
sngpl O
, O
10 O
ki O
bohat O
idara O
idara O
. O

newsdesk O
chitral B-LOC
kasmir O
awam O
! O
pakistan O
teen O
monsoon B-MISC
bank O
report O
19 O
maeeshat O
maeeshat O
hum O
eid B-MISC
unicef B-ORG
. O

swat B-LOC
ppp B-ORG
conflict O
magar O
lahore B-LOC
magar O
. O
17 O
11 O
diplomacy O
se O
idara O
! O
un B-ORG
conflict O
fatima B-PER
noman B-PER
pmln B-ORG
report O
: O
awam O
nizam B-PER
border O
karachi B-LOC
un B-ORG
foreign O
; O

afnan O
zubair B-PER
ecp B-ORG
policy B-MISC
2 O
election B-MISC
fauj O
policy B-MISC
mein O
parliament O
yeh O
- O
mandi O
rajanpur B-LOC
tajzia O
, O

statebank B-ORG
pmln B-ORG
hangu B-LOC
, O
monsoon B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
tax O
ziyada O
qaumi B-ORG
trade B-MISC
election B-MISC
ko O
market O
26 O
usman B-PER
saad B-PER
market O
par O
trade B-MISC
bank O
- O
yeh O
bank O
teen O
fia B-ORG
tax O
gdp B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
? O

fizza O
fatima B-PER
ramzan B-MISC
stadium O
coach O
player O
stadium O
islamabad B-LOC
coach O
lahore B-LOC
team O
idara O
is O
player O
stadium O
ko O
par O
player O
- O
tajzia O
match O
. O

iba B-ORG
jhelum B-LOC
ya O
agar O
rawalpindi B-LOC
skardu B-LOC
masla O
, O
relief B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
rajanpur B-LOC
maeeshat O
par O
tax O
karachi B-LOC
, O

festival B-MISC
kashif B-PER
ayesha B-PER
sehat B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
tajzia O
disease O
education B-MISC
disease O
education B-MISC
disease O
vaccine B-MISC
nizam B-PER
flood B-MISC
woh O
taleem B-MISC
education B-MISC
hospital O
agenda O
aabadi B-MISC
! O

talha B-PER
rabia B-PER
vaccine B-MISC
scholarship B-MISC
score O
stadium O
team O
cricket B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
stadium O
pakistan O
islamabad B-LOC
score O
. O
ko O
! O

kpk B-LOC
peshawar B-LOC
lums B-ORG
summit B-MISC
barh O
tum O
ka O
conflict O
par O
border O
bohat O
conflict O
conflict O
foreign O
lahore B-LOC
conflict O
un B-ORG
treaty O
30 O
un B-ORG
treaty O
24 O
border O
- O

bahawalpur B-LOC
icc B-ORG
foreign O
report O
treaty O
abhi O
foreign O
bilateral O
treaty O
innovation O
relief B-MISC
waqas B-PER
summit B-MISC
tajzia O
ko O
hussain B-PER
conflict O
un B-ORG
swabi B-LOC
chakwal B-LOC
bilateral O
qaumi B-ORG
aur O
mein O
tum O
? O

who B-ORG
bahawalpur B-LOC
multan B-LOC
budget B-MISC
report O
trade B-MISC
bank O
larkana B-LOC
tak O
bank O
budget B-MISC
tum O
gdp B-MISC
tax O
hum O
peshawar B-LOC
hunza B-LOC
zara B-PER
fizza O
pakistan O
budget B-MISC
; O

hina B-PER
agenda O
budget B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
rajanpur B-LOC
mandi O
coach O
kafi O
kafi O
pakistan O
koi O
pti B-ORG
statebank B-ORG
score O
; O

metro O
nadra B-ORG
punjab B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
un B-ORG
hum O
nizam B-PER
teen O
magar O
. O
agar O
nizam B-PER
skardu B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
ke O
budget B-MISC
market O
? O
10 O
trade B-MISC
ya O
. O

skardu B-LOC
statebank B-ORG
un B-ORG
se O
bilateral O
innovation O
tak O
treaty O
karachi B-LOC
. O
border O
summit B-MISC
summit B-MISC
22 O
conflict O

sidra B-PER
sngpl O
report O
arslan B-PER
election B-MISC
government O
government O
aku B-ORG
railways O
minister O
startup O
ek O
policy B-MISC
parliament O
parliament O
11 O

camp B-MISC
ahmed B-PER
idara O
disease O
hospital O
hospital O
ka O
ka O
flood B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
tak O
flood B-MISC
ek O
tum O
flood B-MISC
; O
awam O
; O

hina B-PER
imf B-ORG
government O
government O
policy B-MISC
awam O
fauj O
. O
hukumat O
- O
hukumat O
government O
fauj O
fauj O
islamabad B-LOC
barh O
fakhar B-PER
election B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
camp B-MISC
fauj O
adalat O
policy B-MISC
isi B-ORG
nadra B-ORG
report O
report O
. O

agenda O
fawad B-PER
sarfaraz B-PER
hospital O
covid B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
! O
: O
exports B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
awam O
imf B-ORG
education B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
aabadi B-MISC
thar B-LOC
dir B-LOC
sehat B-MISC
disease O
aabadi B-MISC

imran B-PER
sui O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
election B-MISC
government O
parliament O
; O
government O
minister O
minister O
23 O
hukumat O
! O

railways O
fia B-ORG
vehari B-LOC
rajanpur B-LOC
education B-MISC
tax O
; O
sngpl O
trade B-MISC
? O
10 O
karachi B-LOC
imports B-MISC
nizam B-PER
19 O
: O
inflation B-MISC
pakistan O
imf B-ORG
tajzia O
har O
. O

ecp B-ORG
muzaffarabad B-LOC
gilgit B-LOC
29 O
budget B-MISC
? O
bank O
tax O
: O
maeeshat O
29 O
hina B-PER
amna B-PER
! O

election B-MISC
waqas B-PER
sumaira B-PER
aur O
sehat B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
mansehra B-LOC
masla O
aabadi B-MISC
abhi O
vaccine B-MISC
disease O
aabadi B-MISC
education B-MISC
magar O
tajzia O
hum O
nizam B-PER
sehat B-MISC
20 O
: O
dengue B-MISC
28 O
14 O
islamabad B-LOC
se O
! O

kashif B-PER
kashif B-PER
isi B-ORG
teen O
parliament O
fauj O
fauj O
agar O
unicef B-ORG
fauj O
: O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
islamabad B-LOC
ek O
? O

parliamenttv O
ziarat B-LOC
tax O
idara O
dengue B-MISC
trade B-MISC
26 O
farhan B-PER
rizwan B-PER
education B-MISC
gilgit B-LOC
is O
report O
19 O
ek O
bank O
islamabad B-LOC
mardan B-LOC
: O

arslan B-PER
saba B-PER
nadra B-ORG
radio O
ek O
karachi B-LOC
idara O
do O
kam O
2 O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
election B-MISC
tak O
policy B-MISC
2 O
! O
hukumat O
newsdesk O
fauj O
government O
report O
, O
masla O
ptcl O
1 O
karachi B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
hukumat O
: O

talha B-PER
edhi B-ORG
unicef B-ORG
adalat O
pmln B-ORG
government O
policy B-MISC
parliamenttv O
qaumi B-ORG
government O
government O
camp B-MISC
parliament O
tajzia O
adalat O
fauj O
exports B-MISC
; O

ecp B-ORG
chakwal B-LOC
larkana B-LOC
trade B-MISC
, O
24 O
awam O
balochistan B-LOC
hunza B-LOC
ek O
budget B-MISC
idara O
babar B-PER
ahmed B-PER
; O
edhi B-ORG
ecp B-ORG
nizam B-PER
budget B-MISC
ziyada O
? O

rescue1122 O
pso O
hyderabad B-LOC
gujranwala B-LOC
bank O
is O
trade B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
trade B-MISC
market O
bank O
2 O
inflation B-MISC
nizam B-PER
tax O
7 O

imran B-PER
samina B-PER
verdict B-MISC
education B-MISC
shehbaz B-PER
stadium O
21 O
coach O
nizam B-PER
stadium O
ko O
; O
karachi B-LOC
masla O
score O
har O
? O
, O
cricket B-MISC
awam O
: O

iftikhar B-PER
unicef B-ORG
parliament O
pakistan O
ka O
par O
7 O
par O
fauj O
hukumat O
lahore B-LOC
government O
parliament O
karachi B-LOC
29 O
, O

festival B-MISC
summit B-MISC
naeem O
pakistan O
covid B-MISC
education B-MISC
agenda O
exports B-MISC
, O
aabadi B-MISC
: O
abhi O
pakistan O
qaumi B-ORG
21 O
flood B-MISC
disease O
hospital O
karachi B-LOC
monsoon B-MISC
ki O
? O

pcb B-ORG
mardan B-LOC
ko O
? O
qaumi B-ORG
mein O
tax O
inflation B-MISC
- O
ki O
market O
karachi B-LOC
ko O
lahore B-LOC
tax O
bank O
gdp B-MISC
bohat O
main O
rescue1122 O
hamid B-PER
idara O
budget B-MISC
tax O
report O
qaumi B-ORG
tax O
! O

metro O
narowal B-LOC
pakistan O
market O
inflation B-MISC
edhi B-ORG
pso O
pmln B-ORG
awam O
mardan B-LOC
mandi O
bohat O
maeeshat O
market O
sindh B-LOC
ecp B-ORG
maeeshat O
ko O
inflation B-MISC
market O
bank O
- O

waqar O
eid B-MISC
exports B-MISC
hamid B-PER
waqar O
; O
maryam B-PER
koi O
30 O
match O
yeh O
player O
match O
player O
islamabad B-LOC
abhi O
har O
nizam B-PER
tum O
qaumi B-ORG
team O

talha B-PER
pemra B-ORG
pemra B-ORG
ko O
policy B-MISC
policy B-MISC
tak O
fauj O
karachi B-LOC
parliament O
election B-MISC
14 O
parliament O
danish B-PER
waqar O
par O
swabi B-LOC
fauj O
ki O
aap O
tajzia O
pakistan O

dir B-LOC
ptcl O
icc B-ORG
par O
conflict O
border O
conflict O
foreign O
diplomacy O
conflict O
nust B-ORG
border O
sana B-PER
karachi B-LOC
treaty O
masla O
ke O
21 O
foreign O
abhi O
ke O
nust B-ORG
hum O
diplomacy O
foreign O
se O
bilateral O
suparco B-ORG
: O

rizwan B-PER
flood B-MISC
pakistan O
stadium O
player O
team O
5 O
player O
match O
tajzia O
player O
team O
mein O
stadium O
, O
stadium O
tournament O
team O
report O
nizam B-PER
- O

hassan B-PER
startup O
agenda O
awam O
match O
player O
coach O
pakistan O
masla O
coach O
bohat O
player O
score O
. O

pia B-ORG
ogdcl B-ORG
abbottabad B-LOC
peshawar B-LOC
lekin O
aap O
gdp B-MISC
budget B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
pakistan O
inflation B-MISC
barh O
aabadi B-MISC
trade B-MISC
market O
gdp B-MISC
teen O
maeeshat O

monsoon B-MISC
innovation O
jamal O
qaumi B-ORG
disease O
sehat B-MISC
disease O
har O
sehat B-MISC
nizam B-PER
vaccine B-MISC
flood B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
report O
pmln B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
hospital O
sehat B-MISC
magar O
disease O
lums B-ORG
vaccine B-MISC
report O
hospital O
; O

gdp B-MISC
hamza B-PER
13 O
islamabad B-LOC
vaccine B-MISC
? O
taleem B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
disease O
tak O
23 O
masla O
hospital O
lahore B-LOC
education B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
ke O
masla O
ka O
tajzia O
pia B-ORG
worldbank B-ORG
hospital O
aap O
disease O
25 O
shaheen B-PER
vaccine B-MISC
: O

kohat B-LOC
nadra B-ORG
lahore B-LOC
ke O
un B-ORG
un B-ORG
, O
summit B-MISC
idara O
tum O
conflict O
un B-ORG
summit B-MISC
rajanpur B-LOC
chitral B-LOC
ziyada O
summit B-MISC
verdict B-MISC
5 O
radio O
. O
ya O
; O

pso O
lahore B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
market O
pakistan O
karachi B-LOC
budget B-MISC
bohat O
budget B-MISC
barh O
maeeshat O
tax O
magar O
maeeshat O
gdp B-MISC
tajzia O
inflation B-MISC
un B-ORG
karachi B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
market O
nizam B-PER
tax O
lekin O
aur O
inflation B-MISC
market O
budget B-MISC
kafi O
, O

jibran O
jibran O
nadra B-ORG
ecp B-ORG
agar O
1 O
hukumat O
policy B-MISC
ayesha B-PER
policy B-MISC
imf B-ORG
parliamenttv O
koi O
report O
tak O
sahiwal B-LOC
mardan B-LOC
election B-MISC
parliament O
peshawar B-LOC
larkana B-LOC
agar O
policy B-MISC
barh O
22 O
? O

rizwan B-PER
uet B-ORG
government O
inflation B-MISC
policy B-MISC
awam O
qaumi B-ORG
pakistan O
. O
adalat O
budget B-MISC
hukumat O
6 O
? O

hussain B-PER
hec B-ORG
islamabad B-LOC
! O
chitral B-LOC
adalat O
nizam B-PER
government O
qaumi B-ORG
fauj O
thar B-LOC
sahiwal B-LOC
policy B-MISC
kam O
hukumat O
23 O
government O
magar O
parliament O
tum O
adalat O
, O

danish B-PER
sehat B-MISC
19 O
masla O
sehat B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
imf B-ORG
awam O
sarfaraz B-PER
player O
main O
match O
team O
lahore B-LOC
stadium O
ko O
barh O
tajzia O
team O
ki O
quetta B-LOC
; O

rizwan B-PER
budget B-MISC
do O
match O
, O
idara O
ka O
lahore B-LOC
kamran B-PER
tajzia O
player O
iba B-ORG
tournament O
tournament O
is O
kafi O
ka O
tournament O
lahore B-LOC
21 O
islamabad B-LOC
report O
team O
8 O
- O

samina B-PER
scholarship B-MISC
flood B-MISC
tajzia O
cricket B-MISC
29 O
. O
isi B-ORG
team O
karachi B-LOC
16 O
team O
! O
30 O
ke O
shehbaz B-PER
tournament O
? O

dir B-LOC
sui O
iba B-ORG
masla O
magar O
is O
conflict O
, O
do O
diplomacy O
hec B-ORG
nab B-ORG
quetta B-LOC
attock B-LOC
ya O
summit B-MISC
muzaffarabad B-LOC
kashif B-PER
. O

pmln B-ORG
chitral B-LOC
abbottabad B-LOC
bank O
inflation B-MISC
maeeshat O
rizwan B-PER
bank O
6 O
tax O
karachi B-LOC
barh O
bank O
gdp B-MISC
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
barh O
14 O
imran B-PER
ka O
islamabad B-LOC
trade B-MISC
market O
karachi B-LOC
; O

fizza O
rescue1122 O
6 O
hum O
hukumat O
! O
parliament O
lahore B-LOC
election B-MISC
nizam B-PER
hukumat O
election B-MISC
. O
30 O
nizam B-PER
nizam B-PER
. O

lahore B-LOC
rescue1122 O
ke O
muzaffarabad B-LOC
un B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
un B-ORG
treaty O
barh O
kasur B-LOC
conflict O
bilateral O
border O
har O
se O
; O

humaira O
lums B-ORG
lahore B-LOC
agar O
fauj O
nizam B-PER
election B-MISC
government O
nizam B-PER
kyunke O
masla O
adalat O
20 O
qaumi B-ORG
abhi O
karachi B-LOC

sana B-PER
wapda B-ORG
1 O
adalat O
hockey B-MISC
government O
election B-MISC
abbottabad B-LOC
sukkur B-LOC
parliament O
parliament O
hukumat O
sngpl O
adalat O
4 O
suparco B-ORG
ppp B-ORG
- O

waqar O
jamal O
icc B-ORG
railways O
koi O
sindh B-LOC
vehari B-LOC
minister O
is O
fauj O
hukumat O
hukumat O
policy B-MISC
do O
adalat O
barh O
mein O
idara O
lahore B-LOC
wapda B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
, O

ppp B-ORG
pia B-ORG
larkana B-LOC
jhelum B-LOC
tum O
maeeshat O
nizam B-PER
inflation B-MISC
idara O
lahore B-LOC
pmln B-ORG
kafi O
: O
camp B-MISC
earthquake B-MISC
agenda O
earthquake B-MISC
maeeshat O
barh O
, O
trade B-MISC
budget B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
, O
gdp B-MISC
bank O
monsoon B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
? O
? O

zubair B-PER
worldbank B-ORG
government O
parliament O
report O
barh O
qaumi B-ORG
election B-MISC
awam O
government O
minister O
adalat O
islamabad B-LOC
masla O
tajzia O
kafi O
hukumat O
government O
adalat O
teen O
24 O
minister O
masla O
tajzia O
fauj O
? O

naeem O
roadmap O
match O
rizwan B-PER
sarim B-PER
25 O
tajzia O
karachi B-LOC
tournament O
tajzia O
abhi O
idara O
cricket B-MISC
player O
islamabad B-LOC
score O
report O
masla O
match O
match O
tournament O
: O

unicef B-ORG
aku B-ORG
gujranwala B-LOC
larkana B-LOC
ziarat B-LOC
teen O
budget B-MISC
maeeshat O
30 O
khuzdar B-LOC
rawalpindi B-LOC
market O
gdp B-MISC
nizam B-PER
earthquake B-MISC
flood B-MISC
market O
budget B-MISC
hum O
se O
gdp B-MISC
lekin O
aap O
gdp B-MISC
teen O
trade B-MISC
- O

worldbank B-ORG
swat B-LOC
muzaffarabad B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
idara O
inflation B-MISC
woh O
trade B-MISC
trade B-MISC
nizam B-PER
bank O
- O
market O
gdp B-MISC
report O
11 O
gdp B-MISC
budget B-MISC
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
12 O

sui O
punjab B-LOC
mardan B-LOC
is O
hum O
market O
pakistan O
teen O
tum O
gdp B-MISC
se O
market O
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
bank O
gdp B-MISC
pakistan O
18 O
ka O
ziarat B-LOC
kashif B-PER
, O

sindh B-LOC
fia B-ORG
report O
diplomacy O
un B-ORG
un B-ORG
barh O
conflict O
pemra B-ORG
pti B-ORG
? O
report O
sngpl O
icc B-ORG
imran B-PER
- O
un B-ORG
un B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
summit B-MISC
bilateral O
lahore B-LOC
, O

psl B-ORG
psl B-ORG
nowshera B-LOC
tajzia O
nizam B-PER
nizam B-PER
nizam B-PER
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
market O
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
qaumi B-ORG
30 O
5 O
bank O
? O

sindh B-LOC
peshawar B-LOC
psl B-ORG
un B-ORG
; O
aap O
zara B-PER
islamabad B-LOC
treaty O
foreign O
border O
. O
nowshera B-LOC
swat B-LOC
border O
se O
conflict O
- O

parliamenttv O
pemra B-ORG
mansehra B-LOC
masla O
trade B-MISC
lekin O
trade B-MISC
teen O
. O
trade B-MISC
report O
ahmed B-PER
qaumi B-ORG
inflation B-MISC
? O

ali B-PER
suparco B-ORG
nepra O
election B-MISC
15 O
22 O
lahore B-LOC
masla O
! O
bohat O
ziyada O
dera B-LOC
fauj O
idara O
hukumat O
fauj O
election B-MISC
24 O
awam O
sukkur B-LOC
parliament O
ek O
aap O
policy B-MISC
adalat O
yeh O
11 O
har O
! O

mandi O
statebank B-ORG
21 O
summit B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
hina B-PER
border O
un B-ORG
ahsan B-PER
foreign O
karachi B-LOC
bilateral O
border O
ziyada O
8 O
! O

iba B-ORG
vehari B-LOC
attock B-LOC
budget B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
maeeshat O
budget B-MISC
nizam B-PER
gdp B-MISC
babar B-PER
sumaira B-PER
tajzia O
is O
idara O
, O

sajid O
fia B-ORG
statebank B-ORG
fauj O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
jamal O
babar B-PER
policy B-MISC
election B-MISC
government O
islamabad B-LOC
barh O
! O
election B-MISC
is O
hukumat O
election B-MISC
skardu B-LOC
par O
hukumat O
report O
khadija B-PER
taleem B-MISC
? O

rescue1122 O
pso O
swabi B-LOC
tax O
budget B-MISC
maeeshat O
qaumi B-ORG
budget B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
swat B-LOC
; O
sadia B-PER
maryam B-PER
masla O
kam O
tax O
bank O
pakistan O
nizam B-PER
? O
idara O
gdp B-MISC
budget B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
budget B-MISC

sarfaraz B-PER
startup O
har O
qaumi B-ORG
uet B-ORG
rescue1122 O
! O
report O
cricket B-MISC
okara B-LOC
faisalabad B-LOC
barh O
islamabad B-LOC
- O
26 O
? O

saba B-PER
newsdesk O
ogdcl B-ORG
fauj O
parliament O
government O
! O
is O
mein O
barh O
fauj O
ek O
fauj O
har O
mein O
election B-MISC
parliament O
idara O
par O
tajzia O
kam O
thar B-LOC
barh O
- O

kasur B-LOC
statebank B-ORG
pso O
idara O
sana B-PER
rabia B-PER
treaty O
treaty O
30 O
lahore B-LOC
diplomacy O
exports B-MISC
foreign O
un B-ORG
verdict B-MISC
ramzan B-MISC
conflict O
nizam B-PER
worldbank B-ORG
imports B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
. O

hearing B-MISC
bilal O
hassan B-PER
covid B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
tum O
taleem B-MISC
tajzia O
! O
20 O
. O
tak O
aabadi B-MISC
teen O
! O

waqar O
verdict B-MISC
stadium O
match O
match O
barh O
8 O
stadium O
match O
chakwal B-LOC
mein O
lahore B-LOC
team O
cricket B-MISC
stadium O
, O

flood B-MISC
imran B-PER
iftikhar B-PER
aabadi B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
se O
bohat O
aabadi B-MISC
ya O
mirpur B-LOC
okara B-LOC
ya O
teen O
disease O
disease O
flood B-MISC
pakistan O
- O
tak O
- O

sarfaraz B-PER
nepra O
adalat O
policy B-MISC
election B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
; O
election B-MISC
parliament O
minister O
policy B-MISC
policy B-MISC
hum O
fauj O
hukumat O
awam O
fauj O
faisalabad B-LOC
kohat B-LOC
parliament O
ya O
fia B-ORG
fauj O
islamabad B-LOC
, O
government O
aap O
fauj O
. O

ayesha B-PER
statebank B-ORG
parliament O
: O
jibran O
koi O
ke O
islamabad B-LOC
election B-MISC
28 O
ayesha B-PER
policy B-MISC
parliament O
4 O
tajzia O
par O
? O
bohat O
startup O
islamabad B-LOC
, O

hussain B-PER
nadra B-ORG
isi B-ORG
mein O
samina B-PER
edhi B-ORG
adalat O
fauj O
arslan B-PER
ziyada O
bohat O
hukumat O
kam O
nizam B-PER
masla O
danish B-PER
sana B-PER
roadmap O
gdp B-MISC
parliament O
hukumat O
hukumat O
qaumi B-ORG
. O
fauj O
; O

nust B-ORG
rawalpindi B-LOC
pakistan O
bank O
idara O
cholistan B-LOC
bank O
gdp B-MISC
9 O
tajzia O
tak O
15 O
inflation B-MISC
bank O
30 O
maeeshat O
tax O
29 O
bohat O
budget B-MISC
tax O
tax O
maeeshat O
bank O
trade B-MISC
budget B-MISC
! O

innovation O
adnan B-PER
zubair B-PER
hum O
islamabad B-LOC
sialkot B-LOC
kafi O
mein O
hospital O
aabadi B-MISC
, O
camp B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
. O

unicef B-ORG
parliamenttv O
jhung O
larkana B-LOC
report O
tax O
gdp B-MISC
budget B-MISC
maeeshat O
rizwan B-PER
hamza B-PER
10 O
budget B-MISC
koi O
bank O
- O
maeeshat O
7 O
tum O
report O
tax O
inflation B-MISC
trade B-MISC
, O

naeem O
statebank B-ORG
adalat O
. O
qaumi B-ORG
election B-MISC
fauj O
lahore B-LOC
adalat O
minister O
parliament O
ya O
minister O
tum O
vaccine B-MISC
government O
parliament O
abhi O
! O
parliament O
government O
11 O
masla O
mein O
do O
? O

rescue1122 O
abbottabad B-LOC
- O
tax O
ka O
market O
budget B-MISC
11 O
21 O
qaumi B-ORG
bahawalpur B-LOC
barh O
maeeshat O
nizam B-PER
bank O
- O
market O
market O
17 O
qaumi B-ORG
inflation B-MISC
bank O
se O
masla O
? O

noman B-PER
camp B-MISC
stadium O
qaumi B-ORG
kasur B-LOC
gwadar B-LOC
pakistan O
tournament O
cricket B-MISC
, O
? O
, O
tournament O
match O
: O

sidra B-PER
zubair B-PER
earthquake B-MISC
dengue B-MISC
tournament O
team O
. O
islamabad B-LOC
ecp B-ORG
lahore B-LOC
awam O
aap O
score O
cricket B-MISC
tournament O
22 O
2 O
match O
shehbaz B-PER
adnan B-PER
idara O

balochistan B-LOC
khuzdar B-LOC
newsdesk O
agar O
fizza O
babar B-PER
pakistan O
idara O
27 O
conflict O
barh O
border O
sehat B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
ya O
4 O
foreign O
woh O
un B-ORG
! O

chitral B-LOC
kasmir O
statebank B-ORG
wapda B-ORG
conflict O
faisalabad B-LOC
faisalabad B-LOC
idara O
bilateral O
border O
border O
summit B-MISC
border O
barh O
foreign O
jamal O
camp B-MISC
woh O
islamabad B-LOC
un B-ORG
summit B-MISC
masla O
treaty O
karachi B-LOC
? O

suparco B-ORG
imf B-ORG
jhung O
kasmir O
har O
2 O
gdp B-MISC
tajzia O
tax O
se O
lahore B-LOC
maeeshat O
idara O
railways O
budget B-MISC
24 O
magar O
barh O
trade B-MISC
asif B-PER
maryam B-PER
tax O
. O
maeeshat O
: O
inflation B-MISC
woh O
pakistan O
! O

hamza B-PER
monsoon B-MISC
budget B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
match O
coach O
match O
score O
karachi B-LOC
parliamenttv O
cricket B-MISC
stadium O
magar O
match O
tournament O

farhan B-PER
waqas B-PER
exports B-MISC
education B-MISC
match O
20 O
coach O
idara O
coach O
score O
kyunke O
match O
stadium O
ya O
waqar O
5 O
mirpur B-LOC
mansehra B-LOC
kam O
shaheen B-PER
, O

edhi B-ORG
pia B-ORG
narowal B-LOC
tak O
market O
mein O
zara B-PER
mahnoor B-PER
29 O
, O
inflation B-MISC
30 O
pakistan O
gdp B-MISC
idara O
agar O
tax O
bank O
. O

hamza B-PER
amna B-PER
flood B-MISC
tajzia O
masla O
barh O
pakistan O
match O
main O
stadium O
match O
tournament O
stadium O
pakistan O
idara O
idara O
ki O
islamabad B-LOC
tournament O
kam O
mein O
: O

pso O
hyderabad B-LOC
jhelum B-LOC
maeeshat O
koi O
agar O
market O
trade B-MISC
nizam B-PER
nizam B-PER
bank O
aap O
nizam B-PER
market O
qaumi B-ORG
budget B-MISC
budget B-MISC
trade B-MISC
unicef B-ORG
ya O
idara O
: O

education B-MISC
flood B-MISC
samina B-PER
swabi B-LOC
chakwal B-LOC
ek O
aabadi B-MISC
hospital O
flood B-MISC
education B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
woh O
taleem B-MISC
awam O
par O
islamabad B-LOC
education B-MISC
uet B-ORG
kafi O
tak O
eid B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
21 O
bohat O
education B-MISC
! O
taleem B-MISC
6 O
! O

iftikhar B-PER
verdict B-MISC
report O
? O
cricket B-MISC
ek O
yeh O
nizam B-PER
cricket B-MISC
player O
stadium O
tak O
coach O
islamabad B-LOC
charsadda B-LOC
sahiwal B-LOC
11 O
match O
7 O
tajzia O
stadium O
- O
stadium O
lahore B-LOC
fbr B-ORG
match O
cricket B-MISC
ka O

hamid B-PER
ogdcl B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
minister O
27 O
election B-MISC
hukumat O
idara O
15 O
hukumat O
agar O
tajzia O
idara O
fauj O
ya O
parliament O
- O
iftikhar B-PER
hassan B-PER
barh O
awam O
? O

amna B-PER
pemra B-ORG
railways O
parliament O
islamabad B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
government O
worldbank B-ORG
6 O
aabadi B-MISC
idara O
masla O
18 O
! O
! O

sumaira B-PER
hina B-PER
camp B-MISC
roadmap O
player O
pakistan O
score O
team O
cricket B-MISC
radio O
player O
masla O
rabia B-PER
team O
danish B-PER
sajid O
un B-ORG
ahmed B-PER
aur O

wapda B-ORG
worldbank B-ORG
dera B-LOC
waqas B-PER
gdp B-MISC
nizam B-PER
malaria B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
ke O
bank O
maeeshat O
nizam B-PER
budget B-MISC
hum O
trade B-MISC
, O

afnan O
imran B-PER
election B-MISC
ziyada O
stadium O
score O
. O
stadium O
coach O
coach O
team O
. O
hunza B-LOC
idara O
tournament O
match O
stadium O
karachi B-LOC
score O
- O
player O
do O
team O
cricket B-MISC
: O
islamabad B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
score O
: O
- O

monsoon B-MISC
noman B-PER
inflation B-MISC
dengue B-MISC
disease O
sehat B-MISC
disease O
taleem B-MISC
pmln B-ORG
education B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
budget B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
11 O
se O
hassan B-PER
sumaira B-PER
! O
taleem B-MISC
- O

hussain B-PER
pmln B-ORG
nepra O
is O
aur O
exports B-MISC
parliament O
parliament O
ya O
metro O
uet B-ORG
zubair B-PER
election B-MISC
bahawalpur B-LOC
vehari B-LOC
tajzia O
attock B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
15 O
monsoon B-MISC
. O

babar B-PER
jibran O
sehat B-MISC
score O
cricket B-MISC
main O
hunza B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
idara O
coach O
! O
gilgit B-LOC
player O
report O
player O
bohat O
stadium O
team O
karachi B-LOC
stadium O
, O
hum O
team O
quetta B-LOC
; O

samina B-PER
hec B-ORG
karachi B-LOC
hukumat O
hukumat O
: O
; O
jhung O
election B-MISC
- O
ek O
adalat O
malaria B-MISC
ke O
barh O
fakhar B-PER
adalat O
tajzia O
election B-MISC
; O

who B-ORG
chitral B-LOC
hangu B-LOC
16 O
trade B-MISC
trade B-MISC
nizam B-PER
tax O
budget B-MISC
nizam B-PER
faisalabad B-LOC
bank O
barh O
flood B-MISC
innovation O
market O
hamza B-PER
haris B-PER
karachi B-LOC
10 O
zubair B-PER
yasir B-PER
bank O
. O
tax O
market O
islamabad B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
? O

attock B-LOC
pmln B-ORG
newsdesk O
ke O
har O
bilateral O
summit B-MISC
idara O
ka O
treaty O
diplomacy O
magar O
un B-ORG
foreign O
bilateral O
un B-ORG
bilateral O
? O

ali B-PER
policy B-MISC
team O
se O
kafi O
stadium O
player O
kyunke O
karachi B-LOC
masla O
match O
cricket B-MISC
teen O
par O
team O

babar B-PER
policy B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
tournament O
team O
player O
report O
bilal O
sadia B-PER
team O
tournament O
ka O
player O
coach O
kasur B-LOC
29 O
qaumi B-ORG
icc B-ORG
: O

ahsan B-PER
imports B-MISC
coach O
report O
tajzia O
report O
masla O
coach O
player O
player O
nizam B-PER
tak O
18 O
covid B-MISC
team O
qaumi B-ORG
mein O
25 O
trade B-MISC
exports B-MISC
: O

hina B-PER
imf B-ORG
icc B-ORG
hukumat O
main O
lekin O
; O
shaheen B-PER
adalat O
ke O
election B-MISC
minister O
tajzia O
chitral B-LOC
rawalpindi B-LOC
hukumat O
parliament O
, O

amna B-PER
cricket B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
stadium O
coach O
mein O
tournament O
tournament O
magar O
cricket B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
tournament O
stadium O
match O
awam O

fia B-ORG
turbat B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
bank O
budget B-MISC
har O
qaumi B-ORG
pso O
ecp B-ORG
gdp B-MISC
teen O
adnan B-PER
mansehra B-LOC
abbottabad B-LOC
idara O
barh O
gdp B-MISC
. O

talha B-PER
jibran O
rescue1122 O
worldbank B-ORG
parliament O
government O
qaumi B-ORG
adalat O
government O
policy B-MISC
barh O
fauj O
is O
policy B-MISC
mein O
19 O
minister O
parliament O
minister O
minister O
report O
idara O
minister O
qaumi B-ORG
har O
, O

suparco B-ORG
gwadar B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
bank O
gdp B-MISC
budget B-MISC
bank O
masla O
tax O
unicef B-ORG
maeeshat O
maeeshat O
, O
bank O
main O
qaumi B-ORG
29 O
hamid B-PER
haris B-PER
inflation B-MISC
un B-ORG

agenda O
eid B-MISC
hassan B-PER
fakhar B-PER
education B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
parliamenttv O
hospital O
verdict B-MISC
dengue B-MISC
hamid B-PER
bilal O
yeh O
aabadi B-MISC
hospital O
taleem B-MISC
, O

dera B-LOC
ecp B-ORG
ptcl O
main O
! O
report O
ahsan B-PER
conflict O
lahore B-LOC
treaty O
? O
icc B-ORG
diplomacy O
do O
teen O
conflict O
border O
bilateral O
tajzia O
conflict O
border O
fia B-ORG
. O
border O
ke O
ziyada O
border O
barh O
, O

arslan B-PER
education B-MISC
ka O
tournament O
pakistan O
lahore B-LOC
tournament O
stadium O
team O
coach O
score O
7 O
stadium O
tournament O
cricket B-MISC
score O
masla O
sehat B-MISC
; O

jibran O
summit B-MISC
aku B-ORG
nizam B-PER
pmln B-ORG
jhung O
main O
score O
match O
player O
barh O
gdp B-MISC
nizam B-PER
team O
par O
larkana B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
coach O
: O
cricket B-MISC
21 O
lekin O
15 O
: O

nab B-ORG
thar B-LOC
tax O
- O
23 O
yeh O
bank O
market O
tajzia O
bank O
tax O
trade B-MISC
. O
ziyada O
qaumi B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
market O
nizam B-PER
ziarat B-LOC
kpk B-LOC
nizam B-PER
maeeshat O
main O
bank O
magar O
budget B-MISC
22 O
12 O
exports B-MISC
. O

hamid B-PER
sidra B-PER
relief B-MISC
24 O
koi O
team O
score O
vaccine B-MISC
trade B-MISC
fbr B-ORG
player O
match O
cricket B-MISC
score O
qaumi B-ORG
? O
aap O
score O
score O
wapda B-ORG
aap O
? O
asif B-PER
score O
festival B-MISC
team O
match O
idara O

ahmed B-PER
waqas B-PER
hearing B-MISC
trade B-MISC
22 O
stadium O
un B-ORG
tournament O
rawalpindi B-LOC
27 O
bohat O
qaumi B-ORG
stadium O
hum O
team O
sngpl O
cricket B-MISC
player O
score O
masla O
team O
awam O
stadium O
coach O
- O

bahawalpur B-LOC
pti B-ORG
woh O
summit B-MISC
diplomacy O
nizam B-PER
summit B-MISC
18 O
tajzia O
pakistan O
tajzia O
pakistan O
ziyada O
border O
un B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
summit B-MISC
, O
bilateral O
ke O
summit B-MISC
kasmir O
summit B-MISC
imran B-PER
conflict O
barh O
tak O
, O

vehari B-LOC
hec B-ORG
report O
bilateral O
- O
kafi O
border O
maryam B-PER
karachi B-LOC
border O
un B-ORG
diplomacy O
diplomacy O
ka O
! O
qaumi B-ORG
! O
diplomacy O
12 O
foreign O
border O
un B-ORG
summit B-MISC
- O

gwadar B-LOC
uet B-ORG
sehat B-MISC
earthquake B-MISC
11 O
do O
foreign O
bilateral O
summit B-MISC
? O
un B-ORG
ya O
idara O
un B-ORG
, O

metro O
vehari B-LOC
rawalpindi B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
budget B-MISC
maeeshat O
maeeshat O
trade B-MISC
! O
idara O
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
barh O
budget B-MISC
awam O
awam O
gdp B-MISC
gujranwala B-LOC
budget B-MISC
tax O
: O

railways O
thar B-LOC
idara O
tax O
30 O
trade B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
nizam B-PER
gdp B-MISC
budget B-MISC
budget B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
budget B-MISC
bohat O
report O
ppp B-ORG
who B-ORG
! O

sadia B-PER
bilal O
isi B-ORG
fauj O
fauj O
nizam B-PER
government O
adalat O
hussain B-PER
sidra B-PER
report O
policy B-MISC
government O
qaumi B-ORG
election B-MISC
- O
dera B-LOC
fauj O
6 O
fauj O
policy B-MISC
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
election B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
adalat O
policy B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
government O

malaria B-MISC
roadmap O
kashif B-PER
sidra B-PER
sehat B-MISC
idara O
do O
vaccine B-MISC
masla O
hospital O
parliamenttv O
aabadi B-MISC
disease O
ki O
education B-MISC
is O
! O

punjab B-LOC
psl B-ORG
ali B-PER
foreign O
treaty O
abhi O
border O
border O
ramzan B-MISC
barh O
treaty O
main O
bilateral O
diplomacy O
karachi B-LOC
tajzia O
bilateral O
un B-ORG
summit B-MISC
9 O
idara O
karachi B-LOC
bilateral O
lahore B-LOC
diplomacy O
diplomacy O
un B-ORG
un B-ORG
do O
- O

education B-MISC
saad B-PER
10 O
tajzia O
sehat B-MISC
imports B-MISC
magar O
har O
aabadi B-MISC
magar O
innovation O
awam O
education B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
ke O
disease O
taleem B-MISC
sui O
ppp B-ORG
ayesha B-PER
hospital O
: O

ramzan B-MISC
samina B-PER
disease O
sehat B-MISC
tajzia O
education B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
education B-MISC
pakistan O
flood B-MISC
disease O
agar O
21 O
. O
do O
lahore B-LOC
. O
muzaffarabad B-LOC
disease O
sehat B-MISC
pakistan O
ahsan B-PER
26 O
sehat B-MISC
agar O
awam O
- O

aabadi B-MISC
camp B-MISC
farhan B-PER
rabia B-PER
karachi B-LOC
disease O
hospital O
sehat B-MISC
! O
hospital O
se O
hospital O
nizam B-PER
aur O
tajzia O
aabadi B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
flood B-MISC
education B-MISC
flood B-MISC
khadija B-PER
asif B-PER
sehat B-MISC
education B-MISC
lekin O
? O
agar O
! O

parliamenttv O
fia B-ORG
mirpur B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
maeeshat O
trade B-MISC
bank O
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
malaria B-MISC
: O
kyunke O
nizam B-PER
bank O
qaumi B-ORG
awam O
market O
awam O
idara O
awam O
3 O
gdp B-MISC
. O

haris B-PER
hamid B-PER
newsdesk O
unicef B-ORG
parliament O
qaumi B-ORG
election B-MISC
? O
, O
awam O
sajid O
covid B-MISC
hockey B-MISC
minister O
ke O
policy B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
nizam B-PER
election B-MISC
railways O
lahore B-LOC
parliament O
ko O
; O

sana B-PER
nawaz B-PER
startup O
inflation B-MISC
coach O
ke O
tak O
edhi B-ORG
30 O
tournament O
team O
player O
jhung O
mardan B-LOC
par O
player O
lekin O
? O

nadra B-ORG
sindh B-LOC
mardan B-LOC
ke O
aur O
tax O
trade B-MISC
barh O
market O
tax O
market O
lahore B-LOC
trade B-MISC
bank O
gdp B-MISC
do O
gdp B-MISC
bank O
idara O
woh O
masla O
hum O
tax O
lahore B-LOC
bohat O
fbr B-ORG
trade B-MISC
: O

hassan B-PER
imports B-MISC
flood B-MISC
ya O
karachi B-LOC
player O
match O
match O
pakistan O
maryam B-PER
un B-ORG
cricket B-MISC
coach O
tournament O
jhelum B-LOC
chitral B-LOC
player O
. O

okara B-LOC
hyderabad B-LOC
unicef B-ORG
ppp B-ORG
summit B-MISC
rawalpindi B-LOC
gilgit B-LOC
kam O
kam O
awam O
conflict O
un B-ORG
kpk B-LOC
treaty O
treaty O
newsdesk O
summit B-MISC
camp B-MISC
flood B-MISC
border O
12 O
un B-ORG
border O
conflict O
diplomacy O
qaumi B-ORG

rawalpindi B-LOC
nowshera B-LOC
isi B-ORG
pmln B-ORG
24 O
gilgit B-LOC
imports B-MISC
: O
22 O
ka O
summit B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
bilateral O
3 O
islamabad B-LOC
diplomacy O
islamabad B-LOC
: O

metro O
mardan B-LOC
budget B-MISC
yeh O
budget B-MISC
- O
is O
bank O
har O
tax O
, O
ke O
2 O
trade B-MISC
report O
tum O
market O
maeeshat O
bank O
budget B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
budget B-MISC
rescue1122 O
inflation B-MISC
market O

gilgit B-LOC
pmln B-ORG
psl B-ORG
ki O
treaty O
lahore B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
ek O
treaty O
foreign O
12 O
har O
13 O
kam O
ahsan B-PER
hamza B-PER
cholistan B-LOC
, O

ogdcl B-ORG
pemra B-ORG
islamabad B-LOC
ka O
tajzia O
market O
tajzia O
karachi B-LOC
ke O
inflation B-MISC
statebank B-ORG
inflation B-MISC
barh O
5 O
karachi B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
bank O
gdp B-MISC
market O
budget B-MISC
tax O
abhi O
karachi B-LOC
barh O
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
kyunke O
tax O
! O

samina B-PER
startup O
karachi B-LOC
report O
coach O
ko O
pmln B-ORG
rescue1122 O
tournament O
cricket B-MISC
worldbank B-ORG
tournament O
cricket B-MISC
magar O
score O
nizam B-PER
score O
team O
tournament O
coach O
report O
stadium O
masla O
coach O
match O
fatima B-PER
tournament O
score O
; O

railways O
turbat B-LOC
nizam B-PER
masla O
tajzia O
kam O
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
se O
16 O
nizam B-PER
aur O
market O
do O
idara O
karachi B-LOC
nust B-ORG
ecp B-ORG
ek O
tax O
inflation B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
ek O
lekin O
bank O
trade B-MISC
tax O
; O
bank O
. O

gdp B-MISC
fakhar B-PER
kashif B-PER
vaccine B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
18 O
hum O
education B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
hospital O
12 O
sehat B-MISC
pakistan O
! O

suparco B-ORG
ziarat B-LOC
trade B-MISC
, O
inflation B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
woh O
ek O
! O
: O
gdp B-MISC
main O
maeeshat O
bank O
trade B-MISC
who B-ORG
agar O
islamabad B-LOC
sukkur B-LOC
kpk B-LOC
hunza B-LOC
awam O
tax O
inflation B-MISC
kyunke O
trade B-MISC

edhi B-ORG
peshawar B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
par O
tax O
awam O
? O
: O
7 O
nowshera B-LOC
kyunke O
koi O
qaumi B-ORG
market O
pakistan O
gdp B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
market O
tax O
mirpur B-LOC
idara O
! O

newsdesk O
fia B-ORG
kpk B-LOC
14 O
qaumi B-ORG
market O
masla O
? O
budget B-MISC
market O
3 O
report O
inflation B-MISC
budget B-MISC
ppp B-ORG
icc B-ORG
? O
; O
gdp B-MISC
ka O
budget B-MISC
ke O
gdp B-MISC
bank O
market O
, O

saima O
ayesha B-PER
sehat B-MISC
education B-MISC
; O
cricket B-MISC
bohat O
match O
woh O
idara O
ali B-PER
asif B-PER
cricket B-MISC
report O
team O
karachi B-LOC
mein O
nizam B-PER
cricket B-MISC
team O
cricket B-MISC
har O
pakistan O
coach O
ziyada O
awam O
, O

thar B-LOC
dir B-LOC
parliamenttv O
conflict O
8 O
lahore B-LOC
barh O
nizam B-PER
report O
diplomacy O
awam O
28 O
diplomacy O
border O
foreign O
barh O
treaty O
; O

peshawar B-LOC
sngpl O
railways O
treaty O
report O
foreign O
ka O
barh O
sui O
un B-ORG
hum O
qaumi B-ORG
idara O
: O
. O

ayesha B-PER
aku B-ORG
hec B-ORG
newsdesk O
fauj O
kamran B-PER
hec B-ORG
nust B-ORG
12 O
minister O
report O
election B-MISC
parliament O
policy B-MISC
adalat O
adalat O
ali B-PER
! O

icc B-ORG
psl B-ORG
gilgit B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
flood B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
punjab B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
trade B-MISC
; O
pakistan O
bank O
: O
bank O
qaumi B-ORG
, O

rajanpur B-LOC
pso O
23 O
conflict O
diplomacy O
22 O
verdict B-MISC
roadmap O
suparco B-ORG
8 O
treaty O
border O
18 O
ka O
bilateral O
agar O
awam O
islamabad B-LOC
ko O
bohat O
ka O
muzaffarabad B-LOC
: O

zubair B-PER
radio O
lahore B-LOC
adalat O
adalat O
agar O
ki O
policy B-MISC
sui O
? O
election B-MISC
parliament O
yeh O
fauj O
government O
16 O
pakistan O
talha B-PER
? O

ayesha B-PER
startup O
; O
team O
21 O
yeh O
newsdesk O
rizwan B-PER
24 O
ke O
bohat O
thar B-LOC
multan B-LOC
tournament O
koi O
is O
karachi B-LOC
eid B-MISC
player O
election B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
idara O
lahore B-LOC
stadium O
score O
, O

farhan B-PER
festival B-MISC
relief B-MISC
team O
har O
match O
narowal B-LOC
match O
har O
team O
team O
score O
, O
- O

farhan B-PER
mahnoor B-PER
ptcl O
government O
islamabad B-LOC
barh O
hukumat O
minister O
parliament O
policy B-MISC
minister O
flood B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
main O
islamabad B-LOC
punjab B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
fauj O
ki O
tajzia O
election B-MISC
nizam B-PER
election B-MISC
25 O
, O

pcb B-ORG
metro O
gilgit B-LOC
awam O
budget B-MISC
market O
maeeshat O
tax O
bank O
hussain B-PER
ali B-PER
15 O
tax O
yeh O
report O
chakwal B-LOC
teen O
pakistan O
- O

ali B-PER
ramzan B-MISC
coach O
match O
coach O
agar O
agenda O
tournament O
13 O
awam O
cricket B-MISC
nizam B-PER
match O
tajzia O
masla O
cricket B-MISC
barh O
team O
awam O
teen O
! O

mansehra B-LOC
edhi B-ORG
suparco B-ORG
: O
conflict O
conflict O
magar O
rajanpur B-LOC
woh O
qaumi B-ORG
summit B-MISC
pakistan O
border O
! O
is O
un B-ORG
conflict O
19 O
22 O
treaty O
bilateral O
25 O
summit B-MISC
! O

mandi O
sindh B-LOC
lums B-ORG
conflict O
lahore B-LOC
do O
1 O
gdp B-MISC
festival B-MISC
conflict O
ek O
2 O
15 O
treaty O
bilateral O
un B-ORG
ki O
gujranwala B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
taleem B-MISC

fizza O
exports B-MISC
30 O
player O
radio O
report O
rabia B-PER
score O
agenda O
coach O
islamabad B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
score O
player O
unicef B-ORG
ppp B-ORG
tak O
score O
samina B-PER
kamran B-PER
score O
scholarship B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
? O
: O

hec B-ORG
nust B-ORG
turbat B-LOC
rabia B-PER
28 O
mein O
22 O
market O
jibran O
adnan B-PER
maeeshat O
inflation B-MISC
trade B-MISC
: O
tax O
. O

rizwan B-PER
sngpl O
government O
pcb B-ORG
sui O
adalat O
aap O
policy B-MISC
hukumat O
nizam B-PER
policy B-MISC
fauj O
fauj O
government O
26 O
barh O
election B-MISC
? O
; O

exports B-MISC
waqas B-PER
disease O
disease O
14 O
kohat B-LOC
gwadar B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
tajzia O
flood B-MISC
flood B-MISC
pakistan O
flood B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
education B-MISC
education B-MISC
nizam B-PER
? O

gilgit B-LOC
sui O
pakistan O
foreign O
27 O
un B-ORG
24 O
kyunke O
awam O
conflict O
hangu B-LOC
balochistan B-LOC
tajzia O
ke O
foreign O
23 O
report O
nizam B-PER
aur O
! O

saima O
ramzan B-MISC
match O
pakistan O
pakistan O
kafi O
tournament O
? O
15 O
team O
player O
coach O
karachi B-LOC
ko O
se O
karachi B-LOC
score O

who B-ORG
radio O
sahiwal B-LOC
gujranwala B-LOC
report O
inflation B-MISC
har O
barh O
charsadda B-LOC
larkana B-LOC
! O
gujranwala B-LOC
tax O
gdp B-MISC
20 O
main O
tax O
lekin O
narowal B-LOC
! O

fawad B-PER
sadia B-PER
hec B-ORG
uet B-ORG
nust B-ORG
parliament O
26 O
sehat B-MISC
abhi O
! O
13 O
election B-MISC
idara O
pemra B-ORG
kam O
22 O
hukumat O
dera B-LOC
sialkot B-LOC
har O
! O
lekin O
! O

education B-MISC
festival B-MISC
maryam B-PER
17 O
disease O
! O
taleem B-MISC
20 O
nizam B-PER
flood B-MISC
saima O
samina B-PER
flood B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
koi O
main O
? O

haris B-PER
hamid B-PER
aabadi B-MISC
trade B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
ki O
multan B-LOC
player O
score O
match O
par O
har O
sahiwal B-LOC
chitral B-LOC
stadium O

bilal O
danish B-PER
uet B-ORG
; O
. O
21 O
fauj O
agar O
hukumat O
unicef B-ORG
barh O
koi O
barh O
. O

zubair B-PER
saima O
worldbank B-ORG
psl B-ORG
islamabad B-LOC
government O
adalat O
5 O
minister O
do O
election B-MISC
teen O
nizam B-PER
minister O

babar B-PER
pso O
policy B-MISC
government O
muzaffarabad B-LOC
quetta B-LOC
barh O
monsoon B-MISC
festival B-MISC
minister O
29 O
kamran B-PER
hukumat O
policy B-MISC
adalat O
hukumat O

fakhar B-PER
farhan B-PER
psl B-ORG
minister O
adalat O
nepra O
: O
18 O
nizam B-PER
idara O
barh O
bohat O
barh O
masla O
islamabad B-LOC
camp B-MISC
dengue B-MISC
election B-MISC
minister O
policy B-MISC
nizam B-PER
25 O
- O

zubair B-PER
flood B-MISC
innovation O
karachi B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
report O
coach O
un B-ORG
- O
talha B-PER
4 O
idara O
4 O
aap O
ka O
stadium O
lahore B-LOC
stadium O
! O
? O
coach O
tournament O
suparco B-ORG
nust B-ORG
eid B-MISC
14 O
cricket B-MISC
tournament O
newsdesk O
? O

fawad B-PER
icc B-ORG
government O
minister O
hukumat O
par O
hukumat O
idara O
nizam B-PER
parliament O
islamabad B-LOC
policy B-MISC
government O
adalat O
tak O
; O
3 O
government O
government O
tak O
rabia B-PER
barh O
adalat O
monsoon B-MISC
: O
, O

ptcl O
mansehra B-LOC
hangu B-LOC
bank O
gdp B-MISC
, O
bank O
17 O
trade B-MISC
statebank B-ORG
aku B-ORG
barh O
okara B-LOC
; O
sukkur B-LOC
market O
maeeshat O
inflation B-MISC
8 O
hockey B-MISC
trade B-MISC
- O

sarfaraz B-PER
imran B-PER
hec B-ORG
edhi B-ORG
jibran O
sarfaraz B-PER
fauj O
nizam B-PER
adalat O
idara O
karachi B-LOC
policy B-MISC
nizam B-PER
parliament O
10 O
fauj O
hum O
adalat O
hukumat O
hukumat O
pmln B-ORG
! O

lums B-ORG
parliamenttv O
bahawalpur B-LOC
gilgit B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
gdp B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
magar O
islamabad B-LOC
qaumi B-ORG
karachi B-LOC
hassan B-PER
tajzia O
budget B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
tax O
ka O
gdp B-MISC
24 O
inflation B-MISC
trade B-MISC
tax O
budget B-MISC
startup O
scholarship B-MISC
? O

trade B-MISC
bilal O
afnan O
disease O
flood B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
aabadi B-MISC
ko O
sehat B-MISC
30 O
masla O
ke O
taleem B-MISC
sindh B-LOC
pakistan O
karachi B-LOC
; O

edhi B-ORG
psl B-ORG
mardan B-LOC
kohat B-LOC
masla O
bank O
18 O
gdp B-MISC
scholarship B-MISC
awam O
bank O
maeeshat O
nizam B-PER
9 O
masla O
bohat O
- O
psl B-ORG
nust B-ORG
. O
- O
se O
inflation B-MISC
2 O
budget B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
- O

kashif B-PER
arslan B-PER
fia B-ORG
awam O
3 O
government O
policy B-MISC
humaira O
mahnoor B-PER
maryam B-PER
fauj O
verdict B-MISC
har O
minister O
policy B-MISC
2 O
magar O
: O

gdp B-MISC
sarfaraz B-PER
, O
idara O
teen O
vaccine B-MISC
- O
ke O
yasir B-PER
saba B-PER
nawaz B-PER
- O
hospital O
lahore B-LOC
idara O
disease O
tum O
flood B-MISC
? O
teen O
masla O
26 O
ziyada O
tajzia O
kamran B-PER
khadija B-PER
nizam B-PER
vaccine B-MISC
! O

cricket B-MISC
hamid B-PER
masla O
pakistan O
karachi B-LOC
agar O
vaccine B-MISC
hum O
sehat B-MISC
barh O
report O
flood B-MISC
kyunke O
report O
ko O
disease O
education B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
? O
education B-MISC
ke O
11 O
pakistan O
taleem B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
. O
- O

ahmed B-PER
radio O
hockey B-MISC
budget B-MISC
nizam B-PER
election B-MISC
report O
parliament O
policy B-MISC
amna B-PER
adalat O
? O
masla O
? O
; O

pso O
edhi B-ORG
dera B-LOC
sahiwal B-LOC
tax O
karachi B-LOC
trade B-MISC
market O
inflation B-MISC
dengue B-MISC
15 O
18 O
awam O
report O
inflation B-MISC
; O
: O
market O
trade B-MISC
trade B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
trade B-MISC
budget B-MISC
trade B-MISC

hec B-ORG
hangu B-LOC
cholistan B-LOC
kasur B-LOC
isi B-ORG
gdp B-MISC
hum O
report O
1 O
budget B-MISC
; O
tajzia O
ppp B-ORG
worldbank B-ORG
! O

chakwal B-LOC
swabi B-LOC
pti B-ORG
parliamenttv O
vehari B-LOC
rajanpur B-LOC
masla O
treaty O
nizam B-PER
border O
lahore B-LOC
bilateral O
quetta B-LOC
diplomacy O
bilateral O
un B-ORG
conflict O
un B-ORG
foreign O
bilateral O
bilateral O
woh O
22 O
treaty O
ka O
: O

relief B-MISC
rabia B-PER
policy B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
nab B-ORG
taleem B-MISC
idara O
vaccine B-MISC
koi O
attock B-LOC
okara B-LOC
vaccine B-MISC
khadija B-PER
barh O
karachi B-LOC
uet B-ORG
awam O
agar O
sehat B-MISC
har O
sehat B-MISC
disease O
; O

yasir B-PER
summit B-MISC
hec B-ORG
21 O
report O
ya O
. O
stadium O
stadium O
coach O
un B-ORG
- O
ke O
ke O
match O
barh O
: O
player O
coach O
sajid O
danish B-PER
saima O
ramzan B-MISC
team O
tournament O
coach O
dengue B-MISC
tournament O
- O

rizwan B-PER
lums B-ORG
radio O
12 O
nizam B-PER
parliament O
waqar O
hukumat O
masla O
adalat O
hukumat O
woh O
teen O
islamabad B-LOC
fauj O
parliament O
. O

hamid B-PER
ahmed B-PER
dengue B-MISC
hockey B-MISC
sngpl O
cricket B-MISC
aku B-ORG
match O
idara O
ziyada O
player O
thar B-LOC
ek O
magar O
player O
statebank B-ORG
ka O
cricket B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
tajzia O
coach O
qaumi B-ORG
worldbank B-ORG
; O
16 O
ka O
chitral B-LOC
ek O
: O
; O

summit B-MISC
mahnoor B-PER
aur O
har O
ka O
taleem B-MISC
report O
nizam B-PER
barh O
ka O
amna B-PER
aabadi B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
tajzia O
ogdcl B-ORG
? O
aabadi B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
ko O
awam O
? O

waqas B-PER
relief B-MISC
startup O
ka O
se O
player O
stadium O
tajzia O
islamabad B-LOC
coach O
nizam B-PER
skardu B-LOC
player O
. O
stadium O
. O
tournament O
team O
: O

yasir B-PER
ecp B-ORG
; O
par O
ka O
fauj O
policy B-MISC
parliament O
minister O
adnan B-PER
karachi B-LOC
hukumat O
government O
28 O
parliament O
fauj O
aap O
khuzdar B-LOC
- O

newsdesk O
ecp B-ORG
bahawalpur B-LOC
jhelum B-LOC
kyunke O
islamabad B-LOC
budget B-MISC
12 O
khuzdar B-LOC
rawalpindi B-LOC
taxila O
inflation B-MISC
. O
idara O
! O
naeem O
adnan B-PER
tax O
har O
9 O
gdp B-MISC
bohat O
idara O
summit B-MISC
festival B-MISC
tax O
nizam B-PER

arslan B-PER
pti B-ORG
fbr B-ORG
hukumat O
unicef B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
government O
18 O
adalat O
hukumat O
parliament O
report O
awam O
government O
qaumi B-ORG
government O
newsdesk O
policy B-MISC
: O

malaria B-MISC
waqas B-PER
6 O
magar O
education B-MISC
25 O
, O
lahore B-LOC
- O
education B-MISC
uet B-ORG
sehat B-MISC
worldbank B-ORG
flood B-MISC
- O
taleem B-MISC
ek O
vaccine B-MISC
: O
aabadi B-MISC
22 O
disease O
kafi O
: O

iba B-ORG
jhelum B-LOC
18 O
gdp B-MISC
22 O
karachi B-LOC
market O
inflation B-MISC
tax O
idara O
inflation B-MISC
market O
- O
lahore B-LOC
nizam B-PER
awam O
gdp B-MISC
: O
bank O
aur O
; O

ppp B-ORG
skardu B-LOC
sukkur B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
pakistan O
report O
: O
karachi B-LOC
? O
maeeshat O
market O
gdp B-MISC
maeeshat O
nizam B-PER
maeeshat O
bank O
tajzia O
gdp B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
- O
budget B-MISC
- O

railways O
newsdesk O
rajanpur B-LOC
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
attock B-LOC
kasmir O
idara O
budget B-MISC
budget B-MISC
chakwal B-LOC
22 O
bank O
trade B-MISC
nizam B-PER
market O
tax O
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
woh O
nizam B-PER
! O

earthquake B-MISC
hamid B-PER
flood B-MISC
education B-MISC
flood B-MISC
hum O
, O
taleem B-MISC
tak O
education B-MISC
education B-MISC
aur O
disease O
aabadi B-MISC
hospital O
? O
! O

sehat B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
kamran B-PER
: O
hospital O
awam O
flood B-MISC
agenda O
scholarship B-MISC
flood B-MISC
disease O
ki O
kyunke O
taleem B-MISC
. O
taleem B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
tajzia O
disease O
aap O
taleem B-MISC
: O

kpk B-LOC
ppp B-ORG
ecp B-ORG
un B-ORG
border O
pmln B-ORG
ek O
treaty O
foreign O
border O
lahore B-LOC
conflict O
foreign O
border O
islamabad B-LOC
foreign O
foreign O
un B-ORG
, O

verdict B-MISC
scholarship B-MISC
nawaz B-PER
iftikhar B-PER
hospital O
disease O
aur O
nizam B-PER
awam O
fia B-ORG
vaccine B-MISC
disease O
flood B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
hospital O
4 O
vaccine B-MISC
report O
hospital O
report O
15 O
2 O
main O
; O

aku B-ORG
kasur B-LOC
magar O
maeeshat O
nust B-ORG
woh O
unicef B-ORG
idara O
idara O
budget B-MISC
tax O
budget B-MISC
metro O
fbr B-ORG
inflation B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
idara O
aur O
; O
fbr B-ORG
isi B-ORG
- O
karachi B-LOC
? O

bilawal B-PER
camp B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
barh O
tournament O
cricket B-MISC
. O
zubair B-PER
25 O
amna B-PER
player O
- O
nizam B-PER
team O
11 O
player O
. O
sajid O
karachi B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
player O
match O
! O

iftikhar B-PER
statebank B-ORG
nab B-ORG
fia B-ORG
fauj O
awam O
pakistan O
taleem B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
idara O
samina B-PER
aku B-ORG
pso O
tajzia O
: O

danish B-PER
hamza B-PER
hockey B-MISC
tournament O
relief B-MISC
earthquake B-MISC
tournament O
tak O
coach O
12 O
awam O
teen O
score O
30 O
lahore B-LOC
par O
: O

radio O
rajanpur B-LOC
maeeshat O
is O
karachi B-LOC
tax O
; O
gdp B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
maeeshat O
mirpur B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
maeeshat O
ya O
barh O
gdp B-MISC
; O

hockey B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
saima O
nawaz B-PER
lahore B-LOC
sehat B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
education B-MISC
tum O
vaccine B-MISC
27 O
mein O
? O
disease O
karachi B-LOC
sehat B-MISC
mardan B-LOC
mandi O
vaccine B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
aku B-ORG
lekin O
mein O
ya O
3 O
; O

naeem O
statebank B-ORG
lahore B-LOC
policy B-MISC
adalat O
newsdesk O
ecp B-ORG
minister O
hukumat O
barh O
adalat O
adalat O
awam O
fauj O
parliament O
barh O
har O
! O
policy B-MISC
verdict B-MISC
, O

lahore B-LOC
iba B-ORG
metro O
diplomacy O
26 O
conflict O
hum O
awam O
un B-ORG
monsoon B-MISC
ko O
17 O
bohat O
treaty O
ke O
summit B-MISC
summit B-MISC
ppp B-ORG
diplomacy O
border O
bilateral O
treaty O
un B-ORG
bilateral O
agar O
, O

camp B-MISC
sumaira B-PER
vaccine B-MISC
nizam B-PER
taleem B-MISC
disease O
mardan B-LOC
taxila O
education B-MISC
. O
kam O
tak O
hospital O
pakistan O
karachi B-LOC
5 O
aabadi B-MISC
flood B-MISC
danish B-PER
sana B-PER
, O
flood B-MISC
, O

maryam B-PER
nab B-ORG
? O
fauj O
minister O
verdict B-MISC
report O
minister O
ko O
fauj O
nizam B-PER
- O
election B-MISC
? O
bohat O
! O

sadia B-PER
parliamenttv O
edhi B-ORG
policy B-MISC
vehari B-LOC
amna B-PER
woh O
4 O
parliament O
karachi B-LOC
policy B-MISC
parliament O
abhi O
policy B-MISC
camp B-MISC
innovation O
qaumi B-ORG
awam O
ki O
election B-MISC
! O

ahmed B-PER
statebank B-ORG
sngpl O
parliament O
fizza O
minister O
16 O
adalat O
policy B-MISC
20 O
masla O
hukumat O
government O
minister O
mein O
minister O
? O
is O
policy B-MISC
bilawal B-PER
sajid O
tum O
awam O
- O

usman B-PER
summit B-MISC
player O
bohat O
islamabad B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
player O
report O
hum O
pakistan O
coach O
bohat O
ek O
match O
29 O
player O
cricket B-MISC
match O
islamabad B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
. O
quetta B-LOC
stadium O
cricket B-MISC
player O
, O
kam O
woh O
; O

adnan B-PER
isi B-ORG
fbr B-ORG
policy B-MISC
fauj O
noman B-PER
government O
? O
sidra B-PER
pakistan O
adalat O
abhi O
tum O
minister O
15 O
; O

thar B-LOC
jhung O
pia B-ORG
bilateral O
border O
ziyada O
qaumi B-ORG
lums B-ORG
icc B-ORG
magar O
nizam B-PER
conflict O
! O
treaty O
22 O
tajzia O
report O
, O

earthquake B-MISC
ali B-PER
hospital O
vaccine B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
awam O
idara O
hospital O
nizam B-PER
sehat B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
. O
5 O
taleem B-MISC
education B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
! O
26 O
education B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
summit B-MISC
islamabad B-LOC
20 O
; O

sadia B-PER
innovation O
tajzia O
un B-ORG
cricket B-MISC
do O
har O
kasmir O
hyderabad B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
score O
, O
hum O
tournament O

sadia B-PER
policy B-MISC
education B-MISC
coach O
coach O
ko O
tournament O
idara O
kasmir O
team O
dengue B-MISC
bohat O
har O
tournament O
pia B-ORG
koi O
team O
1 O
tournament O
pakistan O
masla O
tournament O
17 O
20 O
score O
ki O
score O
cricket B-MISC

faisalabad B-LOC
charsadda B-LOC
iba B-ORG
woh O
ki O
ahmed B-PER
pakistan O
diplomacy O
foreign O
bilateral O
bilateral O
jibran O
summit B-MISC
hum O
- O
foreign O
21 O
ek O
summit B-MISC
summit B-MISC

ahmed B-PER
who B-ORG
minister O
19 O
gujranwala B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
saad B-PER
kafi O
minister O
minister O
. O
ya O
policy B-MISC
hina B-PER
policy B-MISC
tajzia O
election B-MISC
hukumat O
aur O
minister O
adalat O
election B-MISC
mein O
government O
fauj O
, O
har O
; O
pakistan O
? O

sidra B-PER
dengue B-MISC
monsoon B-MISC
coach O
khadija B-PER
tournament O
stadium O
masla O
nust B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
coach O
stadium O
har O
21 O
har O
- O

kashif B-PER
taleem B-MISC
education B-MISC
coach O
mein O
20 O
match O
mirpur B-LOC
idara O
yeh O
worldbank B-ORG
yeh O
tournament O
; O
team O
17 O
yeh O
coach O
, O

ayesha B-PER
rescue1122 O
pso O
fauj O
policy B-MISC
adalat O
parliament O
agar O
minister O
election B-MISC
government O
exports B-MISC
hukumat O
teen O
qaumi B-ORG
amna B-PER
islamabad B-LOC
tajzia O
fauj O
? O

malaria B-MISC
humaira O
vaccine B-MISC
aur O
1 O
sehat B-MISC
sehat B-MISC
education B-MISC
disease O
ek O
ke O
5 O
waqar O
hamza B-PER
fizza O
! O
, O

iftikhar B-PER
sarfaraz B-PER
inflation B-MISC
ek O
coach O
har O
tournament O
player O
player O
score O
stadium O
stadium O
tournament O
stadium O
kasmir O
khuzdar B-LOC
player O
? O
score O
score O
? O

sarfaraz B-PER
pcb B-ORG
pmln B-ORG
abhi O
qaumi B-ORG
hukumat O
aur O
! O
abhi O
minister O
scholarship B-MISC
festival B-MISC
nab B-ORG
awam O
28 O
minister O
kpk B-LOC
jhung O
policy B-MISC
adalat O
qaumi B-ORG
government O
fauj O
; O
- O

camp B-MISC
kamran B-PER
ppp B-ORG
pemra B-ORG
education B-MISC
disease O
lahore B-LOC
- O
lahore B-LOC
sehat B-MISC
23 O
teen O
disease O
idara O
mein O
hospital O
report O
education B-MISC
earthquake B-MISC
ziyada O
lahore B-LOC
disease O
? O

parliamenttv O
bahawalpur B-LOC
barh O
kam O
: O
26 O
gdp B-MISC
! O
mein O
maeeshat O
gdp B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
18 O
gdp B-MISC
bank O
market O
bank O
gdp B-MISC
tax O
budget B-MISC
trade B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
ka O
nizam B-PER
: O

kashif B-PER
nepra O
lums B-ORG
metro O
nepra O
parliament O
hukumat O
magar O
idara O
- O
kasur B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
adalat O
main O
. O
covid B-MISC
parliament O
election B-MISC
, O
yeh O
parliament O
17 O
adalat O
nizam B-PER
government O
barh O
maryam B-PER
karachi B-LOC
hukumat O
! O

sumaira B-PER
haris B-PER
scholarship B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
team O
barh O
score O
hamza B-PER
saba B-PER
team O
barh O
score O
score O
kafi O
stadium O
ko O
; O

hamza B-PER
babar B-PER
education B-MISC
report O
lahore B-LOC
pcb B-ORG
- O
player O
par O
tournament O
match O
par O
2 O
nizam B-PER
metro O
ppp B-ORG
; O
team O
islamabad B-LOC
ya O
tajzia O
inflation B-MISC
festival B-MISC
- O
aur O
match O
idara O
; O

ali B-PER
election B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
. O
coach O
roadmap O
player O
score O
stadium O
coach O
thar B-LOC
koi O
coach O
zara B-PER
sana B-PER
magar O
stadium O
stadium O
tournament O
? O
ke O
ya O
cricket B-MISC
player O
masla O
; O
: O

hussain B-PER
hamza B-PER
inflation B-MISC
gujranwala B-LOC
bohat O
swabi B-LOC
abbottabad B-LOC
coach O
team O
24 O
abhi O
tajzia O
islamabad B-LOC
coach O
cricket B-MISC
coach O
- O
: O

saba B-PER
shaheen B-PER
camp B-MISC
team O
coach O
score O
ramzan B-MISC
stadium O
score O
: O
awam O
islamabad B-LOC
: O
score O
18 O
? O

sajid O
railways O
policy B-MISC
7 O
policy B-MISC
awam O
inflation B-MISC
peshawar B-LOC
tak O
lahore B-LOC
is O
minister O
minister O
ayesha B-PER
imf B-ORG
adalat O
government O
election B-MISC
government O
psl B-ORG
policy B-MISC
ek O
eid B-MISC

farhan B-PER
naeem O
cricket B-MISC
player O
karachi B-LOC
awam O
coach O
karachi B-LOC
; O
tournament O
report O
agenda O
tajzia O
1 O
woh O
score O
team O
! O

iba B-ORG
metro O
sindh B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
gdp B-MISC
yeh O
idara O
report O
yeh O
par O
barh O
maeeshat O
inflation B-MISC
shaheen B-PER
; O

okara B-LOC
isi B-ORG
barh O
diplomacy O
abhi O
yeh O
main O
un B-ORG
diplomacy O
report O
diplomacy O
conflict O
woh O
masla O
? O

hangu B-LOC
psl B-ORG
foreign O
nizam B-PER
kam O
report O
tum O
bilateral O
treaty O
summit B-MISC
summit B-MISC
aur O
foreign O
summit B-MISC
diplomacy O
lahore B-LOC
agenda O
tak O
summit B-MISC
conflict O
ppp B-ORG
pmln B-ORG
8 O
masla O
gwadar B-LOC
nizam B-PER
bilateral O
woh O
: O

mahnoor B-PER
kamran B-PER
agenda O
awam O
larkana B-LOC
okara B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
ke O
koi O
. O
cricket B-MISC
rawalpindi B-LOC
lahore B-LOC
tajzia O
taxila O
? O
islamabad B-LOC
awam O
lahore B-LOC
se O
team O
stadium O
! O

edhi B-ORG
sahiwal B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
main O
gdp B-MISC
! O
23 O
bank O
tax O
karachi B-LOC
un B-ORG
gdp B-MISC
bank O
report O
inflation B-MISC
; O

sana B-PER
sajid O
worldbank B-ORG
hec B-ORG
bahawalpur B-LOC
covid B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
government O
kpk B-LOC
government O
hum O
khadija B-PER
parliament O
18 O
policy B-MISC
do O
parliament O
19 O
: O

ali B-PER
iftikhar B-PER
gdp B-MISC
eid B-MISC
mein O
barh O
islamabad B-LOC
mein O
exports B-MISC
malaria B-MISC
. O
score O
stadium O
karachi B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
: O
- O

hockey B-MISC
jamal O
hockey B-MISC
flood B-MISC
election B-MISC
parliamenttv O
aabadi B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
flood B-MISC
disease O
, O
talha B-PER
education B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
10 O
education B-MISC
, O
barh O
11 O
nizam B-PER
tajzia O
usman B-PER
pakistan O
hospital O
, O

fawad B-PER
rizwan B-PER
nust B-ORG
election B-MISC
hukumat O
qaumi B-ORG
masla O
barh O
! O
? O
parliament O
fauj O
parliament O
ek O
election B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
election B-MISC
hukumat O
maryam B-PER
hum O
government O
fauj O
hukumat O
karachi B-LOC
; O

ali B-PER
nab B-ORG
nadra B-ORG
adalat O
government O
suparco B-ORG
government O
government O
tum O
fauj O
? O
report O
fauj O
policy B-MISC
quetta B-LOC
mandi O
, O

nepra O
bahawalpur B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
trade B-MISC
report O
30 O
19 O
maeeshat O
cholistan B-LOC
28 O
gdp B-MISC
ya O
inflation B-MISC
pakistan O
tax O
inflation B-MISC
lahore B-LOC
railways O
1 O
nizam B-PER
ecp B-ORG
idara O
- O

gwadar B-LOC
uet B-ORG
fbr B-ORG
isi B-ORG
bilateral O
isi B-ORG
hec B-ORG
foreign O
treaty O
un B-ORG
tajzia O
idara O
karachi B-LOC
foreign O
conflict O
mardan B-LOC
nizam B-PER
railways O
: O

ptcl O
dera B-LOC
bank O
fawad B-PER
budget B-MISC
un B-ORG
budget B-MISC
qaumi B-ORG
tum O
inflation B-MISC
market O
tajzia O
, O
trade B-MISC
maeeshat O
pakistan O
9 O
nizam B-PER
budget B-MISC
education B-MISC
aabadi B-MISC
budget B-MISC
tax O
market O
market O
waqas B-PER
; O
budget B-MISC

maryam B-PER
malaria B-MISC
summit B-MISC
match O
monsoon B-MISC
cricket B-MISC
do O
tajzia O
team O
score O
main O
lahore B-LOC
gujranwala B-LOC
is O
islamabad B-LOC
stadium O
stadium O
match O
stadium O
- O
score O
education B-MISC
barh O
team O
dir B-LOC
rajanpur B-LOC
tajzia O
awam O
abhi O
; O

cricket B-MISC
sarfaraz B-PER
humaira O
ziyada O
lekin O
budget B-MISC
vaccine B-MISC
taleem B-MISC
kafi O
aabadi B-MISC
9 O
! O
hospital O
education B-MISC

zubair B-PER
uet B-ORG
barh O
kafi O
idara O
hukumat O
hukumat O
adalat O
- O
abbottabad B-LOC
: O
23 O
karachi B-LOC
- O
do O
government O
adalat O
tajzia O
minister O
election B-MISC
ko O
policy B-MISC
karachi B-LOC
lahore B-LOC

amna B-PER
monsoon B-MISC
pakistan O
qaumi B-ORG
lahore B-LOC
nizam B-PER
awam O
match O
kamran B-PER
mahnoor B-PER
team O
jibran O
babar B-PER
stadium O
dengue B-MISC
team O
match O
ya O
nawaz B-PER
match O
stadium O
report O
. O

ppp B-ORG
pcb B-ORG
gilgit B-LOC
sindh B-LOC
1 O
market O
report O
inflation B-MISC
barh O
qaumi B-ORG
22 O
report O
trade B-MISC
jhung O
inflation B-MISC
8 O
10 O
21 O
- O

jamal O
nepra O
uet B-ORG
adalat O
kyunke O
awam O
- O
: O
kafi O
government O
aap O
government O
fauj O
lekin O
lahore B-LOC
parliament O
islamabad B-LOC
fia B-ORG
railways O
kashif B-PER
adalat O
tum O
12 O
fauj O
adalat O
? O

ziarat B-LOC
pemra B-ORG
railways O
conflict O
treaty O
koi O
hum O
cholistan B-LOC
foreign O
border O
karachi B-LOC
islamabad B-LOC
bilateral O
conflict O
lekin O
! O
diplomacy O
border O
. O

saima O
nepra O
woh O
sumaira B-PER
bilal O
woh O
hearing B-MISC
gdp B-MISC
minister O
parliament O
hyderabad B-LOC
hunza B-LOC
fauj O
adalat O
: O

sarfaraz B-PER
aabadi B-MISC
team O
coach O
player O
match O
barh O
lahore B-LOC
match O
tournament O
gilgit B-LOC
match O
player O
match O
shaheen B-PER
jibran O
stadium O
tournament O
kyunke O
idara O
cricket B-MISC
coach O
coach O
karachi B-LOC
, O

fatima B-PER
education B-MISC
monsoon B-MISC
pakistan O
barh O
waqas B-PER
jibran O
team O
; O
player O
lahore B-LOC
cricket B-MISC
masla O
. O

kashif B-PER
ppp B-ORG
qaumi B-ORG
danish B-PER
kashif B-PER
25 O
earthquake B-MISC
monsoon B-MISC
do O
barh O
nizam B-PER
karachi B-LOC
rawalpindi B-LOC
karachi B-LOC
nizam B-PER
29 O
awam O
minister O
is O
policy B-MISC
? O

balochistan B-LOC
suparco B-ORG
railways O
border O
conflict O
nizam B-PER
barh O
un B-ORG
conflict O
teen O
2 O
border O
sidra B-PER
; O
: O
magar O
treaty O
- O
diplomacy O
conflict O
2 O
bilateral O
un B-ORG
un B-ORG
idara O
border O
. O

uet B-ORG
statebank B-ORG
hunza B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
trade B-MISC
abhi O
awam O
budget B-MISC
inflation B-MISC
maeeshat O
gdp B-MISC
masla O
, O
! O

pti B-ORG
sahiwal B-LOC
thar B-LOC
inflation B-MISC
maeeshat O
13 O
: O
21 O
report O
10 O
tak O
barh O
worldbank B-ORG
kasmir O
faisalabad B-LOC
budget B-MISC
pakistan O
inflation B-MISC
nawaz B-PER
